<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 105 

<title>FEAR OF A BOT PLANET</title>

<author>Evan Gore &amp; Heather Lombard</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Ships Cockpit. Fry and Leela are standing in front of the couch 
looking out of the windscreen into open space.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
What do you think of the view, Fry?

<character>FRY</character>
It really puts things in perspective. 
I mean, from up here an entire world 
can seem utterly insignificant.

<info>A small planet splats onto the windscreen like a fly onto a 
car. Leela presses a button and the windscreen wiper cleans it 
off.</info>

<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Featuring Gratuitous Alien Nudity.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Pitch. The crew are sat watching what could 
be a baseball game between the New New York Yankees and the Mars 
Greenskins...</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey, nice seats! We're close enough 
to when you knock a player down with 
a beer bottle, he stays down.

<character>FRY</character>
I don't get this. Is blernsball exactly 
the same as baseball?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Baseball? God forbid!

<character>LEELA</character>
Face it, Fry. Baseball was as boring 
as mom and apple pie. That's why they 
jazzed it up.

<character>FRY</character>
Boring? Baseball wasn't -- hmm, so they 
finally jazzed it up?

<info>A player hits the ball. Fry jumps up, cheering.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Home run! Ha ha! Yay! Right?

<info>The ball is attached to a piece of elastic and springs back. 
A player catches it and the momentum carries him so he flies 
through the air with the ball. He reaches out and hits a base.</info>

<character>UMPIRE</character>
Out!

<info>The crowd cheers and Leela writes on her scorecard.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
What just happened? Why is the ball 
on that springy thing?

<character>LEELA</character>
It's traditional. Just like aluminium 
bats and the seventh inning grope.

<info>Another hit. A player jumps to catch the ball but misses it 
and is caught by Bender.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
I got me a souvenir!  Aww, here you 
go, kid!

<info>He hands the player to the boy.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Corridor. Zoidberg comes out of the Gents 
and approaches a vendor.</info>

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
I'd like a jumbo squid log, please.

<character>VENDOR</character>
We don't sell those.

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Alright, alright. Let me have one of 
your young on a roll.

<character>VENDOR</character>
We're outta rolls.

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Fine! Just give me something crawling 
with parasites.

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Pitch. Back in the bleachers, Zoidberg 
eat a hotdog and purrs. The others have hotdogs too. Fry takes 
a bite.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Mmm, at least hotdogs haven't changed.

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey, buddies, who wants popcorn?

Leela Oh, I'll have some.

<character>FRY</character>
Me!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Oh, yes!

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Yes, please, popcorn!

<info>Popping noises come from Bender's chest cabinet. He opens it 
and takes out a large tub of popcorn.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Anyone want butter on that?

<info>He pumps his antenna.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, I'm starting to get the hang of 
this game. The blerns are loaded, the 
count's three blerns and two anti-blerns 
and the infield blern rule is in effect, 
right?

<character>LEELA</character>
Except for the word "blern" that was 
complete gibberish.

<info>Something beeps. The blernsball falls into a hole and some things 
come up in the pitch. The crowd cheers.</info>

<character>MAN</character>
Multi-ball!  Multi-ball!  Blern! Blerrrn!

<info>Another player rides a hover-cycle around the pitch with the 
bases exploding behind him. A bullpen opens and someone comes 
out riding a huge spider. Fry scratches his head in confusion. 
Leela writes on her score card.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Alright! Yes! Miller's on a pace to 
hit 70 blerns!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
He's good, alright. But he's no Clem 
Johnson. And Johnson played back in 
the days before steroid injections were 
mandatory.

<character>BENDER</character>
Clem Johnson? That skin bag wouldn't 
have lasted one pitch in the old Robot 
Leagues! Now Wireless Joe Jackson, there 
was a blern hitting machine!

<character>LEELA</character>
Exactly! He was a machine designed to 
hit blerns! I mean, come on, Wireless 
Joe was nothing but a programmable bat 
on wheels.

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh, and I suppose Pitchomat 5000 was 
just a modified howitzer?

<character>LEELA</character>
Yep.

<character>BENDER</character>
You humans are so scared of a little 
robot competition you won't even let 
us on the field.

<character>FRY</character>
What are you talking about? There's 
all kinds of robots down there.

<character>BENDER</character>
Yeah, doing crap work! They're bat boys, 
ball polishers, sprinkler systems. But 
how many robot managers are there?

<character>FRY</character>
11?

<character>BENDER</character>
Zero!  And what a surprise! Look who's 
scraping up the filth. Is it a human 
child? I wish!

<info>Farnsworth suddenly leans forward, clutching his chest.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Oh, dear Lord!

<character>FRY</character>
What's wrong?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
It's...my...new pager.

<info>He takes his pager out of his lab coat and turns it on. A holographic 
image of Hermes appears in front of him.</info>

<character>HOLO</character>-<character>HERMES</character>
This is Hermes. A package just came 
in. Everyone is to return to the office 
immediately.  Get away, you filthy bird! 
Shoo! Shoo! Professor, turn me off, 
quick!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
I'm sorry, wha?

<info>Holo-Hermes screams. The bird takes off with him and carries 
him towards the roof.</info>

<character>HOLO</character>-<character>HERMES</character>
(shouting) See you at the office!

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The staff are sat around the table.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Admit it: You all think robots are just 
machines built by humans to make their 
lives easier.

<character>FRY</character>
Well, aren't they?

<character>BENDER</character>
I've never made anyone's life easier 
and you know it!

<info>Enter Farnsworth and a bandaged Hermes, who holds a box with 
a Planet Express label on it and "Chapek 9" written on it.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Great news, everyone. You'll be delivering 
a package to Chapek 9, a world where 
humans are killed on sight.

<character>FRY</character>
Why is that great news?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
I'm glad you asked that question, Fry. 
You see, Chapek 9 was colonised centuries 
ago by a murderous crew of radical robot 
separatists.

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh, so just 'cause a robot wants to 
kill humans that makes him a "radical"?

<character>LEELA</character>
Hey, hold on. I understand these robots 
hate humans, but how do they feel about 
humanoid aliens?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
They're not fans.

<character>HERMES</character>
That's why Bender will have to make 
the actual delivery.

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh, I get it, make the robot do all 
the work!

<character>LEELA</character>
This is the first actual work you've 
ever had to do around here.

<character>BENDER</character>
Well I'm not doing it! It's a robot 
holiday.

<character>FRY</character>
Really? Which one?

<character>BENDER</character>
Only Robanukah. The holiest two weeks 
on the robot calendar.

<character>LEELA</character>
Oh, come on, Bender. Last month it was 
Robomadom and before that Robonza.

<character>FRY</character>
Man, that one was a blast!

<character>BENDER</character>
It wasn't just a blast. It was a sacred 
tribute to my ancestral prototypes which 
happened to take the form of a drinking 
contest.

<character>HERMES</character>
Now, look here, Bender. I respect your 
diversity to the extent the law requires 
but you used up all your days off when 
you had that bout with Roberculosis.

<character>BENDER</character>
Alright, I'll go. But so help me, I'll 
hold a grudge against every last stinking 
one of you for the rest of your lives.

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Well then it's settled. So long, everyone!

<info>Ships Cockpit. The ship approaches Chapek 9.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
So let me get this straight: This planet 
is completely uninhabited?

<character>BENDER</character>
No. It's inhabited by robots!

<character>FRY</character>
Oh. Kinda like how a warehouse is inhabited 
by boxes.

<info>Bender mutters to himself.</info>

<info>The ship hovers above the surface of Chapek 9. The cargo bays 
bomb-bay doors open.</info>

<info>Ships Cargo Bay. Leela holds a remote control to operate the 
magnetic winch.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
OK, Bender, we're here. It's time to 
get to work.

<character>BENDER</character>
Yes, Miss Leela. Tote that space barge, 
lift that space pale.

<character>LEELA</character>
Now we can't land on the surface because 
those robots will kill Fry and me. So 
we'll have to stay up here and lower 
you with the winch. And remember: You 
don't know humans, you don't work for 
humans, and, above all, you don't like 
humans.

<character>BENDER</character>
(ironic) I'll try to keep that in mind!

<info>He steps on the winch and Leela lowers it to the ground.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Hmm, he seems pretty angry.

<character>FRY</character>
Yeah, but I guess I'd be kinda angry 
too if I had to go to some uninhabited 
planet.

<character>LEELA</character>
Maybe we ought to do something nice 
for him.

<info>Ships Cockpit. Leela and Fry have decorated it with banners, 
paper bending unit chains and a beer bottle Menorah.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
There! This oughta show that stupid 
robot we care about him.

<info>The phone beeps.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Ah, Bender must be done with the delivery.

<info>Leela answers the call. Bender's face appears on the screen.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
I'm in trouble. They found out I work 
with humans and -- oh, no! Oh, no!

<info>He screams and is dragged off into the darkness. The phone cuts 
to static.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, my God! We have to go down and rescue 
him.

<character>LEELA</character>
No, we can't! They'll kill us on sight.

<character>FRY</character>
W-what are we gonna do?

<character>LEELA</character>
I don't know! I don't know! It's not 
an easy decision. If only I had two 
or three minutes to think about it.

<info>Ships Cargo Bay. Fry and Leela are dressing up in boxes and 
things.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
<character>OK</character>. If we're going to save Bender, we've 
got to look and act exactly like robots.

<character>FRY</character>
(mechanical voice) I am fully operational, 
captain.

<character>LEELA</character>
We'll have to walk like robots, talk 
like robots and, if necessary, solve 
complex differential equations like 
robots.

<character>FRY</character>
I can sorta dance like a robot. Will 
that help?

<info>He sort of dances like a robot. Leela sighs.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry, first of all this is serious. And 
second of all:

<info>She dances like a robot.</info>

<info>Cut to: Chapek 9 Surface. Fry and Leela lower themselves to 
the surface on the winch and come face to face with a huge robot 
complex. They walks towards it and Fry sees his reflection in 
the colander Leela is wearing on her head.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Man, we look stupid. We should've gotten 
store-bought costumes.

<character>LEELA</character>
Yeah, but there wasn't a Woolworth's 
in this quadrant.

<info>Cut to: Outside Robot complex. They reach the gates of the complex 
but are stopped by two huge robot guards.</info>

<character>GUARDBOT #1</character>
Halt!

<character>GUARDBOT #2</character>
Be you robot or human?

<character>LEELA</character>
Robot...we be.

<character>FRY</character>
Uh, yup! Just two robots out roboting 
it up!  Eh?

<character>GUARDBOT #1</character>
Administer the test.

<character>GUARDBOT #2</character>
Which of the following would you most 
prefer? A: A puppy, B: A pretty flower 
from your sweetie, or C: A large properly-formatted 
data file?

<character>GUARDBOT #1</character>
Choose!

<info>Fry and Leela whisper to each other about the answer.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
(whispering) C!  (talking) Is the puppy 
mechanical in any way?

<character>GUARDBOT #2</character>
No. It is the bad kind of puppy.

<character>LEELA</character>
Then we'll go with that data file.

<character>GUARDBOT #2</character>
Correct.

<character>GUARDBOT #1</character>
The flower would also have been acceptable.

<character>GUARDBOT #2</character>
You may pass.

<info>The guardbots fold up like transformers and move to the side 
of the gates. Fry and Leela enter the complex.</info>

<info>Cut to: Robot Complex. Fry and Leela walk down an empty corridor.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Now if you see any robots, just stay 
out of their way.  (shouting) So far, 
so good.

<info>Time Lapse. A robot construction worker is giving directions 
to a robot crane which is building a Tetris wall.</info>

<character>CONSTRUCTIONBOT</character>
Little to the right, there you go.

<character>LEELA</character>
Have you seen this robot?

<info>She shows him a picture of Bender dressed as a magician pulling 
a rabbit out of a hat.</info>

<character>CONSTRUCTIONBOT</character>
Sorry, can't help you.  Hey, watch it! 
Don't drop that there!  Oh!

<info>Time Lapse. Fry and Leela walk past a sign that says "got milk? 
then you're a human and must be killed".</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Come on, Fry, walk like a robot.

<character>FRY</character>
I can't. I have to go to the bathroom.

<character>LEELA</character>
Robots don't have bathrooms.

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, right. I wonder where they smoke 
in high school.

<character>LEELA</character>
Listen. Just go behind those garbage 
cans. I'll stand guard.

<info>Fry does. A robot approaches Fry.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Hurry up, Fry!

<character>ROBOT</character>
Sir? Are you aware that you're leaking 
coolant at an alarming rate?

<character>FRY</character>
Uh...

<character>ROBOT</character>
Lemme just patch you up with some hot 
resin.

<character>FRY</character>
I think the leak's stopping itself. 
Wait. Wait. Yeah, there we go. Wait. 
Yeah!

<character>ROBOT</character>
What sort of robot turns down a free 
blast of searing-hot resin?

<character>LEELA</character>
I'm sorry. My friend and I have to go 
and perform some mindless repetitive 
tasks.

<info>The robot chuckles.</info>

<character>ROBOT</character>
Sounds like a romantic evening. I won't 
keep you.

<info>The robot zooms away and churns up dust. Leela sneezes. The 
robot turns around and growls. Leela kicks it over and she and 
Fry run off. An anti-human patrol van comes and picks up the 
robot.</info>

<character>PATROL OFFICER #1</character>
Get the humanoid.

<character>PATROL OFFICER #2</character>
Get the intruder.

<character>ANNOUNCER</character>
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!

<character>LEELA</character>
Quick! Let's duck in here!

<info>They run into a cinema (Now Showing: It Came From Planet Earth).</info>

<info>Cinema Auditorium. The movie showing is similar to the popular 
horror movies of the 1950's complete with all-American college 
boy and his beautiful yet naive girlfriend. Both robots. The 
robot audience is wearing 3-D glasses.</info>

<character>ANNOUNCER</character>
We interrupt this sound file to bring 
you a terrifying announcement: A non-metallic 
being has been sighted in the vicinity 
of Make Out Point.

<character>RUSTY</character>
Say, Wendy. Your chassis is a little 
scuffed. Mind if I polish it for you?

<info>The bushes rustle.</info>

<character>WENDY</character>
Did you here that, Rusty? It sounded 
like a human.

<character>RUSTY</character>
Relax, Wendy. Humans will never come 
to our defenceless little town. Its 
perfectly safe to let our guard down 
-- even for a second.

<info>A human - actually a robot actor wearing a human costume - appears 
out of some bushes. Wendy screams and it growls, tears off Rusty's 
head and eats it.</info>

<character>HUMAN</character>
I will eat and digest you all with 
my system of mighty organs. Behold!

<info>It opens itself up revealing human organs. The audience gasps.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Wow, the 3-D's great!

<character>LEELA</character>
Mine's not working.

<info>She moves the 3-D glasses back and forth over her eye. In the 
movie the "human" stumbles around, breathes fire and finally 
collapses. It has an arrow in its back. Wendy and an army robot 
approach it.</info>

<character>ARMY ROBOT</character>
Funny, isn't it? The human was impervious 
to our most powerful magnetic fields, 
yet in the end he succumbed to a harmless 
sharpened stick!

<info>He pulls the stick out of the "human" and chuckles.</info>

<character>WENDY</character>
I'm just glad the nightmare is over.

<character>ARMY ROBOT</character>
It'll never be over, Wendy. Even now 
humans are lurking in our playgrounds, 
our breezeways, perhaps even...our movie 
theatres!

<info>He points into the camera at the audience. They scream.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
God help us!

<info>Outside Cinema. The movie has ended and the robots are filing 
out.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
<character>OK</character>. Keep an eye out for Bender.

<character>ROBOT #1</character>
So, what did you think of the movie?

<character>FRY</character>
Umm, too much romance, not enough human 
killing.

<character>ROBOT #2</character>
Yeah, it was a real chick flick.

<info>A loud fanfare.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
What's that?

<character>ROBOT #1</character>
What do you mean "What's that?"? It's 
5 o'clock: Time for the daily human 
hunt.

<info>The robots all take out pitchforks, maces and fire torches and 
file off in the same direction. Fry and Leela follow.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Try to stay with the crowd so no one 
notices how crummy you look.

<info>She is talking to a robot that looks like Fry disguised as a 
robot.</info>

<character>ROBOT #3</character>
Aww, that was uncalled for!

<character>FRY</character>
I'm over here.

<info>The robots congregate around a platform.</info>

<character>ROBOT #4</character>
I heard a human was draining coolant 
behind garbage can 738.

<character>ROBOT #5</character>
I heard they unscrew our lug nuts at 
night and eat them at their human brunches.

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Welcome to a very special human hunt. 
We have with us today a guest who's 
irrational hatred for humans makes me 
look like a human sympathiser!  A newly-arrived 
refugee from Earth, lets hear it for...Bender!

<info>Bender emerges from the shadows and stands at the microphone.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
It's him! He's OK!

<character>BENDER</character>
Death to humans!

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Ahh! It's good to hear his voice!

<character>BENDER</character>
Many said I was too extreme when I first 
called for the annihilation of the human 
species, as well as some of the more 
cunning monkeys. But after living on 
Earth I can tell you that I am, if anything, 
too merciful!

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
My God! He's become evil.  I mean eviler!

<character>BENDER</character>
Thank you! Thank you! And if you enjoyed 
that diatribe then you'll want to purchase 
my spoken word album, just 18.95! Act 
now and you'll get this Bender action 
figurine.

<info>He pulls the string</info>

<character>BENDER FIGURINE</character>
Bite my shiny metal ass!

<info>The robots wave cash.</info>

<character>ROBOT #6</character>
(shouting) Oh, I want one!

<info>Bender takes the money and hands out the figurines from a box.</info>

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Let the hunt begin!

<info>Robots rush off with clubs and start to hit bushes and look 
under rocks.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Now, your basic human is between three- 
and 25-feet tall and is made of a hairy, 
oily goo wrapped in a t-shirt.

<character>ROBOT #1</character>
Is it true they bite your neck, suck 
your transmission fluid and then you 
become a human?

<character>BENDER</character>
Sure, why not?

<info>They look in some bracken.</info>

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Anything in the trap?

<character>BENDER</character>
Nothing. Today's active humans prefer 
a low-calorie bait.

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Well that makes 146,000 unsuccessful 
hunts in a row. But I've got a good 
feeling about tomorrow.

<info>Bender sees a building.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Wait! What's that?

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
That's the old abandoned adult book 
store. Nothing in there except a few 
mouldy old shreds of robot pornography.

<character>BENDER</character>
Hmm, sounds like a breeding ground for 
humans. I'd better check it out.

<info>Adult Book Store. Bender is looking at robot porn - circuit 
diagrams.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh, yeah! You're a bad girl, aren't 
you?

<character>FRY</character>
Psst! Bender!

<character>BENDER</character>
Huh? Wha? You! What the hell are you 
doing here?

<character>FRY</character>
We've been looking for you. Last we 
heard you were under arrest as a human 
sympathiser.

<character>BENDER</character>
I was. But they let me go when I told 
them I killed a million billion humans.

<character>LEELA</character>
Good for you. Now let's all get back 
to the ship.

<character>BENDER</character>
What for?

<character>FRY</character>
We're rescuing you.

<character>BENDER</character>
I don't wanna be rescued.

<character>FRY</character>
Say what?

<character>BENDER</character>
I love this planet. I've got wealth, 
fame and access to the depths of sleaze 
that those things bring.

<character>FRY</character>
But, Bender, we're your friends.

<character>BENDER</character>
Friends? That activates my hilarity 
unit! I'm just a machine to you. You're 
no more friends with me than you are 
with the toaster or the phonograph or 
the electric chair.

<character>FRY</character>
That's not true.

<character>BENDER</character>
Well that's how it feels to me.

<info>There is an awkward silence.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Bye, Bender. I'll miss you.

<character>BENDER</character>
Go on, get out of here before you get 
caught.

<info>Enter the Robot Mayor and some other robots.</info>

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Bender, good news: Your album just went 
gold! What the?

<character>ROBOT #1</character>
It's the humans!

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Bender! Do something!

<info>Bender grabs Fry and Leela.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Uh...got you...you murderous flesh piles!

<info>Robot Hall of Justice. Fry and Leela are in a cage. The judge 
is a Mac computer.</info>

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Your Honour, I intend to demonstrate 
beyond 0.5% of a doubt that these humans 
before us are guilty of the crime of 
being humans. Come to think of it, I 
rest my case!

<character>JUDGE</character>
Thank you, prosecutor. I will now consider 
the evidence.

<info>He begins to consider. A blue bar moves across his screen.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, wait a minute! Isn't anyone going 
to defend us?

<character>LEELA</character>
Yeah! I mean he might not have a case 
but I'm genuinely not a human.

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Quiet, human!

<info>The judge stops considering. A prompt box shows up on his screen: 
Sorry A System Error Occured [Restart</info> The court gasps in shock.]

<character>ROBOT BAILIFF</character>
Uh-oh! He froze up again!

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Try control alt delete.

<character>ROBOT #1</character>
Jiggle the cord.

<character>ROBOT #2</character>
Turn him off and on.

<character>ROBOT #3</character>
Clean the gunk out of the mouse.

<character>FRY</character>
Call technical support.

<character>ROBOT BAILIFF</character>
OK, OK, he's back online.

<character>JUDGE</character>
I find the defendants - guilty!

<info>The court cheers.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
No!

<character>LEELA</character>
Look! One eye! Count them: One! Not 
human!

<character>JUDGE</character>
The humans are hereby sentenced to live 
as robots live on Earth. They will perform 
tedious calculations and spot-weld automobiles, 
until they become obsolete and are given 
away to an inner-city middle school.

<info>The court cheers again.</info>

<character>ROBOT MAYOR</character>
Great work, Bender! You've taught us 
to hate humans all over again!

<info>Bender chuckles and sighs. The bailiff pulls a lever and Fry 
and Leela fall through the floor.</info>

<info>Cut to: Room. It is pitch black. Fry and Leela hit the floor.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Are you alright?

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, yeah.

<info>The lights come on. Fry is upside down. They are sat before 
five tall robots. Leela gasps.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Who are you?

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
We are the robot elders.

<character>FRY</character>
You don't look very old.

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Thanks. We try to take care of ourselves.

<character>LEELA</character>
What's going on here?

<character>RED ELDER</character>
Silence! Bring in Bender.

<info>The doors open. Enter Bender.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Alright, let's make this quick, I'm 
due at the opening of a mini-mall. Hey! 
What is this?

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Silence! It is time to put the humans 
to death.

<info>Fry and Leela gasp.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
But the judge already sentenced us at 
the trial!

<character>RED ELDER</character>
Silence! That was just a show for the 
public. We are the true rulers of this 
planet, hand carved from meteorites 
by the Robot Founders over four centuries 
ago.

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Silence! Come forward Bender. You will 
have the honour of executing the prisoners.

<character>GREEN ELDER</character>
Silence! I concur!

<character>YELLOW ELDER</character>
Here: Use the ceremonial killer-ma-jig.

<character>BENDER</character>
Uh, I'm a little tired right now. Would 
it be alright if I just gave 'em a savage 
beating?

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
No! The Elders have spoken. Show us 
the killing skills than have made you 
a media darling.

<character>GREEN ELDER</character>
Do it now! Kill them before they bring 
down our whole society!

<character>ELDERS</character>
(chanting) Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it! 
Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it! Do 
it! Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!

<character>BENDER</character>
Aww!  I can't kill them. Plenty of humans 
have mistreated robots but not these 
two. They're my friends. Humans are 
no threat to us. They're stupid, putrid 
cowards.

<character>FRY</character>
Damn right!

<character>BENDER</character>
The fact is, humans are completely harmless.

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
We're well aware of that.

<character>BENDER</character>
You are?

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Of course. But they're useful to us 
as a scapegoat to distract the public 
from their real problem.

<character>GREEN ELDER</character>
Like our crippling lug nut shortage.

<character>ORANGE ELDER</character>
And a corrupt government of incompetent 
Robot Elders.

<character>YELLOW ELDER</character>
Duh, that's for sure.

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Quiet, Jimmy.

<character>BENDER</character>
Well, I'm glad we got all that out in 
the open. We'll just let ourselves out.

<character>GREEN ELDER</character>
Silence! You all know too much.

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Elders: Execute function, control, shift, 
kill!

<info>They form a line and sharp things come out of their arms. They 
move towards Fry, Leela and Bender who back away. Fry suddenly 
leaps forward.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Stop! Take one more step and I'll breathe 
fire on you!

<info>The Elders exchange glances.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
He'll do it. He's crazy!

<character>YELLOW ELDER</character>
Can they really breathe fire or did 
we make that up?

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
Gee, I can't remember anymore! It might 
just be from that stupid movie.

<character>ORANGE ELDER</character>
Was that the original or the re-make?

<info>The crew sneak away.</info>

<character>BLUE ELDER</character>
I don't -- hey! They're getting away.

<info>Chapek 9 Surface. Outside the robot complex, Fry, Leela and 
Bender run towards the winch with hundreds of robots chasing 
them. They jump onto it and Leela presses the button.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
So long, suckers!  Uh, hello, suckers!

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey, hold on a second, I forgot to deliver 
the package.

<info>He hands the parcel to a robot. It loses its balance and falls, 
along with the rest of the robots. The parcel bursts open.</info>

<character>ROBOT #7</character>
Lug nuts! Precious lug nuts!

<character>ROBOT #8</character>
Hooray for the humans!

<info>Ships Cockpit. The ship speeds out of orbit of Chapek 9. Bender 
sees the decorations.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Wow, I can't believe you guys did all 
this for me! This is the best Robanukah 
ever!

<character>FRY</character>
We wanted to show you that we really 
do respect your robot heritage.

<character>BENDER</character>
Aww, thanks! You do know that I made 
Robanukah up to get out of work, right?

<character>LEELA</character>
Of course.

<character>FRY</character>
But that doesn't make it any less meaningful.

<character>BENDER</character>
In that case, let the dancing begin! 
Hey, you guys are good. How the hell 
do you do that?

<info>The crew enjoy the party and take several photos of the occasion.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>