<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 106 

<title>A FISHFUL OF DOLLARS</title>

<author>Patric M. Verrone</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Fry's Bedroom. Fry is awoken by squeaking bed springs from the 
apartment next door. He growls.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I can't take it anymore! They've been 
at it for hours!  (shouting) Give it 
a rest, you two!

<info>Cut to: Next Door Apartment. The robots next door are sat playing 
poker. They have springy bodies which are constantly squeaking. 
One of the robots oils his springs.</info>

<character>ROBOT</character>
(shouting) Sorry!

<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Loading...</info>

<info>Fry's Bedroom. Fry is asleep.</info>

<info>Fade to: Fry's Dream. He is in a packed lecture hall. An old 
teacher stands at the front of the room. She wears frosted half-moon 
glasses and has grey hair.</info>

<character>TEACHER</character>
Good morning, class. I trust you've 
all prepared for today's final exam.

<character>FRY</character>
Uh, excuse me? I missed a few lectures. 
Uh, what subject is this?

<character>TEACHER</character>
Ancient Egyptian algebra.

<info>She points to the blackboard, revealing it is filled with Egyptian 
hieroglyphs. Fry gasps.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
What a nightmare!

<character>TEACHER</character>
Mister Fry, are those your underpants? 
Young man, I think it's time you learned 
a lesson about Lightspeed brand briefs.

<info>She pulls down a poster showing the briefs.</info>

<character>ANNOUNCER</character>
(voice-over) Lightspeed fits today's 
active lifestyle. Whether you're on 
the job......or having fun... Lightspeed 
briefs. Style and comfort for the discriminating 
crotch.

<info>Like an advertisement, a pair of lightspeeds appear in front 
of a flashing background.</info>

<info>Cut to: Fry's Bedroom. The dream ends and Fry suddenly wakes 
up.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
What a weird dream! I'll never get back 
to sleep.

<info>He falls asleep instantly.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The crew are sat around the table.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
So you're telling me they broadcast 
commercials into people's dreams?

<character>LEELA</character>
Of course.

<character>FRY</character>
But, how is that possible?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
It's very simple. The ad gets into your 
brain just like this liquid gets into 
this egg.  Although in reality it's 
not liquid, but gamma radiation.

<character>FRY</character>
That's awful. It's like brainwashing.

<info>Leela wipes the yolk from her hair.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Didn't you have ads in the 20th century?

<character>FRY</character>
Well, sure, but not in our dreams. Only 
on TV and radio. And in magazines and 
movies and at ball games and on buses 
and milk cartons and t-shirts and written 
in the sky. But not in dreams. No siree!

<character>BENDER</character>
Quit squawking, flesh wad, nobody's 
forcing you to buy anything.

<character>AMY</character>
Yeah. I mean we all have commercials 
in our dreams but you don't see us running 
off to buy brand name merchandise at 
low, low prices.

<info>After a long silence they get up and run out.</info>

<info>Alien Overlord &amp; Taylor. A department store. Enter the Planet 
Express staff who are immediately preyed on by a saleswoman at 
the cosmetics stand.</info>

<character>SALESWOMAN</character>
Hi! Care to sample the latest fragrance 
from Calvin Clone?

<character>AMY</character>
No thanks.

<info>The saleswoman sprays her. Amy curses in Chinese and walks away 
rubbing her eyes.</info>

<character>SALESWOMAN</character>
And you, sir?

<character>BENDER</character>
No thanks I --

<info>The saleswoman sprays him. Bender sprays her back with oil, 
covering her face. She coughs and splutters.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Leela is sat on a chair at the cosmetics stand. 
A cosmetologist brushes away her fringe.</info>

<character>COSMETOLOGIST</character>
What a lovely face. We just need to 
draw attention away from the eye area.

<info>She zaps Leela with something and then holds up a mirror. Leela 
sees her reflection and sighs. The woman has plastered her face 
in lipstick so she looks like a clown. In the menswear department 
Fry picks up a box of the briefs.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Cool.  Can I try these on before I buy 
them?

<character>SALESMAN</character>
I'm afraid I can't let you open the 
package. But you can try on the demo 
pair.

<info>He pulls out a pair of smelly underpants and sprays them with 
deodorant.</info>

<info>Fitting Room. Fry puts the briefs and is impressed.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
: Ooh! Ho ho ho!

<info>He sees his reflection in the mirror - a muscled man surrounded 
by women. Then he sees the notice: Objects In The Mirror Are 
Less Attractive Than They Appear and sighs.</info>

<info>Alien Overlord &amp; Taylor. In the robot accessories department, 
Bender, wearing a green sweater, picks up a few cans of Mom's 
Old Fashion Robot Oil from a pile and hides them under the sweater.</info>

<character>AMY</character>
Hey, Bender! Great new sweater.

<character>BENDER</character>
New? What sweater? I came in with it. 
I don't know you people!

<info>He walks off. A hovering <character>CCTV</character> camera follows him. Back in the 
menswear department, Fry is buying the Lightspeeds.</info>

<character>SALESMAN</character>
$30, please.

<character>FRY</character>
$30? I can't afford that. Unless... 
Do you take Visa?

<character>SALESMAN</character>
Visa hasn't existed for 500 years.

<character>FRY</character>
American Express?

<character>SALESMAN</character>
600 years.

<character>FRY</character>
Discover card?

<character>SALESMAN</character>
Sorry we don't take Discover.

<info>Amy, Leela, Zoidberg and Bender walk up behind him.</info>

<character>AMY</character>
Hey! You're springing for Lightspeed? 
Pretty ritzy!

<character>FRY</character>
No, I can't afford them. Being poor 
sucks. What kind of world is this where 
they advertise things not everybody 
can afford?

<character>AMY</character>
Quiet. There's an ad coming on.

<info>On the screens an old woman, the same woman from on the tins 
of oil - Mom - sits in a chair knitting. She is wearing a huge 
green dress and an apron around her front. Behind her on the 
wall is a picture of three men dressed in the same grey clothes.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
Hello shoppers. It's me, Mom!

<character>FRY</character>
Hey who's the rocker jockey?

<character>AMY</character>
Guh! It's Mom. The world's most huggable 
industrialist.

<character>MOM</character>
Call me old fashioned, but when my 
robot starts to squeak like an old screen 
door well, that's when I reach for a 
can of Mom's Old Fashioned Robot Oil.

<character>BENDER</character>
Mmm, tasty!

<character>MOM</character>
And remember: Mom's oil is made with 
10% more love than the next leading 
brand!

<info>She smiles.</info>

<character>ANNOUNCER</character>
"Mom", "love" and "screen door" are 
registered trademarks of Mom Corp.

<info>The tins under Bender's sweater squeak.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, Bender. Sounds like you could use 
a little of that oil.

<info>Some tins fall out of Bender's sweater. Seven hovering <character>CCTV </character>
cameras surround him. He looks up at them.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
I'm boned.

<character>SMITTY</character>
Freeze scuzzbot!

<character>BENDER</character>
Uh, there's obviously been some sort 
of a mistake here.  I'm sure there's......I 
say I'm sure there's......that is, I'm 
sure there's...a very...reasonable...

<info>And some more.</info>

<info>Outside New New York Police Department. On a sign outside is 
Ask About Our Generous Brutality Settlements.</info>

<info>Cut to: New New York Police Department. At the front desk Fry 
counts some money.</info>

<character>AMY</character>
Do we have enough money to pay Bender's 
fine?

<character>FRY</character>
78, 79. 79.50. Crud! We're 50 cents 
short.

<character>LEELA</character>
I'd love to chip in, but Bender stole 
my wallet.

<info>Fry sees something through a window, a building called Big Apple 
Bank.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, that's my old bank. Maybe my account's 
still open.

<info>Big Apple Bank. Fry steps forward to the desk and has a retina 
scanned.</info>

<character>TELLER</character>
Hmm. We don't seem to have your retina 
scan, your fingerprint or your colonic 
map on file.

<character>FRY</character>
Yeah, well, I did open the account over 
a thousand years ago. What about my 
<character>ATM</character> card?

<info>The teller pulls out an old <character>ATM</character> machine from under the desk 
and blows the dust off it.</info>

<character>TELLER</character>
Do you still remember your <character>PIN</character> number?

<character>FRY</character>
Sure! It's the price of a cheese pizza 
and a large soda back where I used to 
work, Panucci's Pizza.

<character>TELLER</character>
OK, you had a balance of 93 cents...

<info>Fry looks at Amy and Leela.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Alright!

<character>TELLER</character>
...and at an average of 2 and a quarter 
percent over a period of 1000 years, 
that comes to...$4.3 billion.

<info>Fry stares for a moment and suddenly starts hyperventilating 
and foaming at the mouth. Then he faints.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The crew are gathered in celebration, 
wearing top hats and drinking champagne.</info>

<character>HERMES</character>
To Fry.

<character>AMY</character>
Cheers!

<info>They raise their glasses.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
I know Fry's rich, but do we really 
have to wear these top hats?

<character>BENDER</character>
Maybe you don't understand just how 
rich he is. In fact, I think I'd better 
put on a monocle.

<info>And he does.</info>

<info>Le Spa. Fry lives the high life. At Le Spa Fry and Leela get 
a relaxing massage and Bender gets a buffing.</info>

<info>Famous-Painting-Shooting. Next, Fry and Leela walk down a corridor 
past many famous paintings. Fry stops at the Mona Lisa, points 
to it and buys it. The corridor is just a wall in the open countryside 
with paintings hanging on it. A man loads the painting into a 
catapult and fires it. Fry, Bender and Leela raise their lasers 
and shoot it, blasting it to pieces.</info>

<info>Original Cosmic Ray's Pizza. The Planet Express staff are gathered 
around a table for lunch.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Pizza dinner on me!  Just keep the tab 
under $50 million.

<character>ROBOT CHEF</character>
Yo!  I haven't got all day. What kind 
of pizza yous guys want?

<character>FRY</character>
Uh, yeah. We'll have one with everything 
but anchovies and one with my all time 
favourite topping, anchovies!

<character>ROBOT CHEF</character>
(mechanical voice) Invalid selection. 
(normal voice) Yo, what are you talking 
about?

<character>FRY</character>
Anchovies? You know? Those little headless 
fish?

<character>ROBOT CHEF</character>
(mechanical voice) Does not compute. 
Does not compute.

<info>His head explodes.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
I'm sorry, Fry, but the anchovy has 
been extinct since the 2200's.

<character>FRY</character>
What?!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Oh, my, yes. Fished to death. Just about 
the time your people arrived on Earth 
wasn't it, Zoidberg?

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
(defensively) I'm not on trial here.

<character>FRY</character>
So none of you has ever had anchovies? 
Oh, man! You don't know what you're 
missing. They were all salty and oily 
and they melted in your mouth and --

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Stop! Stop! I admit it! My people ate 
them all! We kept saying "One more can't 
hurt" and then they were gone. We're 
sorry!

<info>He holds his claws to his head and hangs it in shame. Fry sighs.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I just wished I could've showed you 
guys how great they were. I may be rich 
but I still can't buy back all the things 
I miss from the 20th century.

<character>BENDER</character>
Maybe you're forgetting just how rich 
you are.  Huh? Huh?

<info>Outside Historic 20th Century Apartments. A banner outside advertises 
"With Original Asbestos". On the steps Fry shakes hands with 
the landlord and moves in.</info>

<info>Historic 20th Century Apartment. Amy, Bender and Leela are already 
in there. Amy picks up the telephone is puzzlement and puts the 
receiver over her eyes. Enter Fry.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
So? What do you think?

<character>LEELA</character>
I know you spent a lot of money on this 
place, Fry, but it's awfully primitive. 
The floors are made of such hard wood.

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey! Get a load of this pathetic 20th 
century TV!

<character>FRY</character>
What's wrong with it?

<character>BENDER</character>
Well, aside from causing eye cancer, 
these things had a lousy low-definition 
picture.

<character>AMY</character>
That's true. On a TV like this I bet 
you couldn't even make out my obscene 
tattoo.

<info>She rolls her sleeve up to reveal her obscene tattoo which appears 
blurry. Bender whistles and Leela chuckles.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
That's cute!

<info>Staadgi &amp; Staadgi Auctioneers. In the crowded room Fry bids 
for something.</info>

<character>AUCTIONEER</character>
Sold!

<character>FRY</character>
Yes!

<character>LEELA</character>
I just don't get it. Who was this Ted 
Danson? And why would you pay $10,000 
for his skeleton?

<character>FRY</character>
I have an idea for a sitcom.

<character>BENDER</character>
Ah, leave him alone, Leela. So he's 
going a little wacko with his money. 
It's <character>OK</character>.

<character>LEELA</character>
You're just saying that because he bought 
you that antique robot toy.

<info>Bender chuckles.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Yeah, it is cute.

<info>He starts playing with a "Knock 'Em, Sock 'Em" toy. One little 
robot punches the other's head off and Bender screams.</info>

<character>AUCTIONEER</character>
Now, our final item: This unopened can 
of Angry Norwegian brand anchovies circa 
1997.

<character>FRY</character>
Anchovies?!

<character>AUCTIONEER</character>
The last known can in existence guaranteed 
fresh and edible. Do I hear $10,000?

<character>FRY</character>
15,000!

<character>MAN</character>
20!

<info>A rich Decapodian woman stands up.</info>

<character>DECAPODIAN WOMAN</character>
30! No, 40!

<character>FRY</character>
50,000!

<info>The other bidders whisper to each other.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Are you crazy? It's a can of old fish.

<character>FRY</character>
Don't tell me how to spend my money.

<character>AUCTIONEER</character>
50 going once, twice...

<info>He raises his gavel but is interrupted by Mom.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
75,000.

<info>The room gasps. Mom is stood at the back of the room with the 
three men from the picture in the ad.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Oh, my God, it's Mom! I've never seen 
her in person before.

<character>FRY</character>
100,000.

<info>More whispering from the bidders.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry, you can't bid against Mom. She's 
the richest, most powerful person in 
the world. And she's so adorable.

<info>Mom looks in her purse.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
Well, I suppose I could go as high as...300,000.

<character>FRY</character>
500!

<character>MOM</character>
Oh, mercy be. A million.

<character>FRY</character>
Two.

<character>MOM</character>
Six.

<character>FRY</character>
14!

<character>MOM</character>
I can see the nice young man really 
wants those little fish. Nevertheless, 
I'll bid 23 million.

<info>Fry stands up and raises his hand.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
One jillion dollars.

<info>The bidders gasp in shock.</info>

<character>AUCTIONEER</character>
Sir, that's not a number.

<info>The bidders gasp again.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Oh. In that case, 50 million.

<info>Mom turns to three men behind her.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
Well, boys, your old mother knows when 
she's been beat.  You win, young man. 
I tip my bonnet to you.

<info>The other bidders murmur.</info>

<character>BIDDER #1</character>
Isn't she adorable?

<character>BIDDER #2</character>
Isn't she sweet?

<info>The auctioneer bangs his gavel.</info>

<character>AUCTIONEER</character>
What a class act! Sold! To the gentleman 
who bought every item in today's auction.

<info>Fry stands up an cheers himself but the other bidders boo him.</info>

<info>Historic 20th Century Apartment. Fry wanders around the room 
in the dark and picks up a box.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Now for some good old 20th century <character>TV</character>.

<info>He puts a video tape into the <character>VCR</character>.</info>

<character>ANNOUNCER</character>
Do you remember a time when chocolate 
chip cookies came fresh from the oven? 
Petridge Farm remembers.

<character>FRY</character>
Ah, those were the days.

<character>ANNOUNCER</character>
Do you remember a time when women couldn't 
vote and certain folk weren't allowed 
on golf courses? Petridge Farm remembers.

<info>A knock at the door.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry? Are you there?

<character>FRY</character>
Eh?

<info>Enter Leela and Bender. Fry turns the TV off.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
You haven't been to work in three days. 
What have you been doing?

<character>FRY</character>
I've been sitting right here. I picked 
up my life exactly where I left off 
a thousand years ago. Now if you'll 
excuse me it's 8 o'clock. Time to get 
biz-ay!

<info>Fry turns the stereo on and listens to Baby Got Back by Sir 
Mix-a-lot. Leela turns it off.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
You can't just sit here in the dark 
listening to classical music.

<character>FRY</character>
I could if you hadn't turned on the 
lights and shut off the stereo.

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry, this isn't healthy. You're living 
in the past.

<character>FRY</character>
I'm rich! I can live whenever I want.

<character>LEELA</character>
But we're your friends and we live here 
in the year 3000.

<character>BENDER</character>
Yeah. Now are you gonna come to the 
squid fights with us or sit here wallowing 
in your prehistoric junk?

<character>FRY</character>
Junk? Maybe you can't understand this 
but I've finally found what I need to 
be happy, and it's not friends: It's 
things.

<info>He gets up and walks towards the door. Bender turns around.</info>

<character>BENDER </character>(<character>SADLY</character>)
I'm a thing.

<character>FRY</character>
Just leave me alone.

<info>Fry opens the door and Leela and Bender walk out.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry please.   My ponytail's caught in 
the door.

<character>FRY</character>
I don't need them. Not when I have my 
antique videos, my bucket of fossilised 
<character>KFC</character> and 50 million dollars worth of 
anchovies.

<info>He kisses the tin of anchovies.</info>

<info>Mom's Friendly Robot Company Building Corridor. Mom walks towards 
her office, followed by her sons.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
Mercy me, what a day.

<info>Cut to: Mom's Office.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
Could you shut the door, Igner dear? 
I think I feel a draught coming on. 
Holy crap, that bastard's itchy!  Walt! 
Cream soda!

<info>Walt is the oldest. He has a full head of black hair.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
Right away, mother.  Larry, get your 
mother a cream soda.

<character>LARRY</character>
But Mom said --

<info>Walt slaps him.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
You heard me.

<info>Mom drinks the can of soda, throws it down then lights a cigarette.</info>

<character>IGNER</character>
What's wrong, Mommy?

<character>MOM</character>
It's those damned anchovies. That dirtbag, 
Fry, must know their secret. And I won't 
rest until I get my hands on them. No 
one messes with Mom!

<info>She laughs evily. Walt laughs with her. Larry and Igner join 
in. Walt slaps Larry.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
Quiet, you!

<info>Time Lapse. Mom is now sat behind a huge desk.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
As you boys know, one of the cornerstones 
of my empire is Mom's Old Fashioned 
Robot Oil. Think of it: 10 billion robots. 
Each one needing an oil change every 
3000 miles. You don't have to do the 
math to know that's a buttload of oil.

<character>IGNER</character>
Can I wear your fat suit?

<character>MOM</character>
(shouting): No, Igner, put that down.

<info>Igner drops the fat suit arm.</info>

<character>IGNER</character>
Aww.

<character>WALT</character>
What does this have to do with the anchovies?

<character>MOM</character>
I'm getting to the freaking anchovies. 
A single drop of the anchovies natural 
oil would lubricate 10 robots permanently.

<character>LARRY</character>
Wow, it's a shame they went extinct.

<character>MOM </character>(<character>SHOUTING</character>)
No it isn't, shut your filthy trap! 
(talking) Thank you, Walt. If anyone 
ever got a hold of anchovy <character>DNA</character>, they 
could chop out the oil-making gene, 
stick it in a bunch of third world kids 
and bam! Cheap effective robot oil. 
Enough to put dear old Mom out of businness.

<character>WALT</character>
My God! This Mr. Fry must be a mastermind 
of the highest order.

<info>Cut to: Historic 20th Century Apartment. Fry is sat in the dark 
watching Sanford &amp; Son.</info>

<character>FRED</character>
Esther, you ugly!

<info>Fry laughs.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mom's Friendly Robot Company Building: Mom's Office.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
We have only one option: We'll have 
to bankrupt Mr Fry, so he'll be forced 
to sell the anchovies to us.

<character>WALT</character>
Mother, you are one clever old skag!

<character>MOM</character>
And don't you forget it!

<character>LARRY</character>
But how are we supposed to get Fry's 
money out of the bank?

<character>MOM</character>
That part will be easy, thanks to the 
nice people at Mom's Old Fashioned Video 
Surveillance Unit.

<info>She puts another tape in. The scene at Big Apple Bank replays 
on the <character>TV</character>.</info>

<character>TELLER </character><info>ON TV</info>
Do you still remember your <character>PIN</character> number?

<character>FRY </character><info>ON TV</info>
Sure! It's the price of a cheese pizza 
and a large soda back where I used to 
work, Panucci's Pizza.  It's the price 
of a cheese pizza and a large soda --

<info>Mom turns the TV off.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
You know what needs to be done.

<character>LARRY</character>
What?

<character>MOM </character>(<character>SHOUTING</character>)
Get his <character>PIN</character> number, you idiots!  (talking) 
Now I'm off to some chairty BS for knocked-up 
teenage sluts.

<info>Historic 20th Century Apartment. There is a knock at the door.</info>

<character>WALT </character><info><character>FROM OUTSIDE</character></info>
Mr. Fry. It's those three plumbers you 
called for.

<character>LARRY </character><info><character>FROM OUTSIDE</character></info>
We're here to tighten your drains.

<info>The sounds of Walt's hand meeting Larry's face is heard. Fry 
opens the door.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I didn't order any --

<info>Walt and Igner jump on Fry and pin him to the floor.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
Quick! Give him the tranquilliser.

<info>Larry puts some tablets in Fry's mouth and strokes them down 
his throat.</info>

<character>LARRY</character>
That's a good boy.

<info>Fry falls unconscious.</info>

<info>Pizzeria Set. Fry comes around and sees a disguised Walt wearing 
a fake handlebar moustache.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
Wake up, Mr. Fry.

<character>FRY</character>
Where am I?

<character>WALT</character>
You're in the good old year 2000, working 
here at Panucci's Pizza. You fell asleep 
on the job.

<character>FRY</character>
That sounds like me but, I thought I 
got frozen. Wasn't I in the future?

<character>WALT</character>
No, you only "dreamed" you were in the 
year 3000.

<character>FRY</character>
So I'm really back? That's exactly what 
I wanted, I guess. Who are you?

<character>WALT</character>
I'm Mr. Panucci.

<character>FRY</character>
You are? Did you grow a moustache since 
last night?

<info>Walt tears off the moustache.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
No. Now go work the currency register. 
I think I hear a customer coming...I 
said "I think I hear a customer coming"!

<info>Cut to: Backstage. Larry is forcing a dress over Igner's head. 
Pamela Anderson's head in jar is on a table.</info>

<character>ANDERSON</character>
Hurry up, please. I wanna get back to 
the head museum.

<character>LARRY</character>
Don't worry, Miss Anderson, this won't 
take long. Now, your motivation is you're 
back in the year 2000 and your head's 
still on your body, and you want a cheese 
pizza.

<info>He picks up the jar and puts it on Igner's head.</info>

<character>ANDERSON</character>
OK, but I'm only doing this so people 
will take my head seriously as an actress.

<info>Cut to: Pizzeria Set. Fry notices something on a sign above 
him.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, look! Anchovies!

<character>WALT</character>
Of course. They're not extinct yet. 
And if you need further proof that this 
is really a thousand years ago well, 
here's contemporary actress, Pamela 
Anderson!

<info>Enter Pamela Anderson on top of Igner.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Ooh!

<character>ANDERSON</character>
Hello, Fry. Remember me from Baywatch: 
The Movie?

<character>FRY</character>
Uh...

<character>ANDERSON</character>
It was the first movie to be shot entirely 
in slow motion.

<info>Walt leans in to Anderson.</info>

<character>WALT </character>(<character>WHISPERING</character>)
It hasn't been made yet.

<info>Walt shakes his head.</info>

<character>WALT</character>
Nope.

<character>ANDERSON</character>
Crap!

<character>FRY</character>
Wait. You're Pamela Anderson! Cool! 
What can I get you?

<character>ANDERSON</character>
Oh, I'll have a cheese pizza and a large...uh...line?

<info>Larry whispers from backstage.</info>

<character>LARRY </character>(<character>WHISPERING</character>)
Soda!

<character>ANDERSON</character>
Oh, right! Cheese pizza and a large 
soda!

<character>FRY</character>
Uh, cheese and a --  That was quick!

<character>ANDERSON</character>
So. What do I owe you?

<character>FRY</character>
10.77. Same as my <character>PIN</character> number.

<info>Walt, Larry, Igner and Anderson laugh. Fry is unsure of what 
is happening so just laughs along with them.</info>

<character>IGNER</character>
Hey, you don't get to laugh.

<info>He hits Fry on the head with Anderson's jar.</info>

<info>Outside Historic 20th Century Apartments. A white limo pulls 
up outside and the brothers throw Fry out onto the pavement. 
There are bags of money in the limo.</info>

<info>Cut to: Limo. Igner is driving.</info>

<character>IGNER</character>
Thanks a billion!

<info>He laughs. Larry counts the cash in the back.</info>

<character>LARRY</character>
More like 4.3 billion!

<info>He laughs with Igner. Walt slaps them both.</info>

<character>IGNER</character>
Ow!

<character>LARRY</character>
Ow!

<info>The limo speeds off and Fry blacks out into a dream.</info>

<info>Cut to: Fry's Dream. Pizza's, 1077's and anchovy tins float 
around him. Leela's and Bender's heads float towards him.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, I had a nightmare I was in the year 
2000 and you guys never existed. I'm 
so glad I'm awake now and you're really 
here.

<character>LEELA</character>
Since when do you care about us?

<character>BENDER</character>
We thought you only cared about cans 
of anchovies and stuffy old songs about 
the buttocks.

<character>FRY</character>
No, that's not true!

<info>Leela and Bender float away.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Goodbye-eee!

<character>BENDER</character>
Wheee!

<info>A pack of Lightspeeds appear in the corner.</info>

<info>Fry comes to. A repobot walks out of his apartment with his 
<character>TV</character>.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Bender! Leela! Don't leave me. Wait 
a minute! Hey, buddy what year is this?

<character>REPOBOT</character>
Uh, 3000.

<character>FRY</character>
3000? Yes! I'm still in the future! 
Life is wonderful!  Wait! What are you 
doing with my stuff?

<character>REPOBOT</character>
Uh, check bounced. We're taking it all 
back.

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, no, my <character>ATM</character> card! My secret <character>PIN</character> number! 
1077. I've got nothing left. Except...

<info>He pulls the tin of anchovies out of his sock.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Leela and Bender are sat on the couch 
and Farnsworth is sat at the table.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
You're Fry's relative. Do you have any 
idea how he got so crazy?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Uh, wha? Oh, yes, they say madness runs 
in our family. Some even call me mad! 
And why? Because I dared to dream of 
my own race of atomic monsters. Atomic 
supermen with octagonal-shaped bodies 
that suck blood out of...

<info>He walks out still blabbering. Enter Fry.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Leela! Bender! I missed you so much!

<character>LEELA</character>
You did? What happened?

<character>FRY</character>
I was robbed. They got everything except 
these.

<info>He holds up the anchovies.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Who did?

<info>Leela gasps at something across the room. Mom is stood in the 
doorway wearing her fat suit.</info>

<character>MOM</character>
Hello, Fry.

<character>LEELA</character>
It's Mom.

<character>MOM</character>
I felt terrible when I heard about your 
money troubles and I thought maybe I 
could help out a sweet young man by 
buying his anchovies.

<character>FRY</character>
Sorry. But the anchovies aren't for 
sale.

<character>MOM</character>
What? Listen, you little bastard. I 
control the robot oil business and I 
won't let you ruin me. How much do you 
want?

<character>FRY</character>
You might as well put that chequebook 
away, because I've discovered something 
even more important. My friends. And 
they aren't worth even a penny to me. 
That's why these anchovies are going 
on a pizza, so I can share the food 
I love with the people I like.

<character>MOM</character>
Holy hell! You're going to eat them? 
Oh, well. Just make sure you eat them 
all. You're a growing boy. Toodle-oo! 
Dumb ass!

<character>FRY</character>
What a nice lady!

<info>Time Lapse. The whole staff except for Zoidberg are gathered 
around the table. Fry opens the tin of anchovies.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
OK, my friends. Get ready for the most 
delicious extinct animal you've ever 
tasted.

<character>AMY</character>
I don't know, I've had cow.  Ew! Gross!

<character>FRY</character>
Ah, no one likes them at first but they'll 
grow on you.

<info>Enter Zoidberg. He sniffs.</info>

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
That stench. That heavenly stench!  
More!

<character>FRY</character>
There aren't any more. And there never 
will be.

<info>Zoidberg tips the table over and moves towards Fry, raising 
his claws.</info>

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
More! More! More! More!

<info>THE END</info></xml>