<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 303

<title>THE CRYONIC WOMAN</title>

<author>J. Stewart Burns</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Not a Substitute for Human Interaction.</info>

<info>Ship's Cockpit. The ship is in the Planet Express hangar and 
Fry and Bender are messing around in the cockpit. Fry flies a 
scale model of the ship around and makes whoosh-y noises, then 
a crackling radio noise.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Giant Space Robot, this is Captain Fry 
of the <character>USS</character> Planet Express Ship; We come 
in peace.

<character>BENDER</character>
Tough luck!

<info>He takes a hammer out of his chest cabinet and knocks the ship 
out of Fry's hands. It lands on the floor and Bender smashes 
it to bits. He and Fry laugh.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Well, we destroyed the toy spaceship. 
Now what are we gonna do?

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey, look! The keys to the real spaceship.

<info>Fry sees the keys in the ignition and turns to Bender.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Do you think we should?

<info>Bender stands up.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
(firmly) Yes, I do.

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Kitchen. At the conference table Zoidberg 
reads a book, Hermes sits with an iMac in front of him and Amy 
eats something with chopsticks. In the kitchen, Leela finishes 
washing a "Universe's #1 Space Pilot" mug and puts it next to 
Fry's "Universe's #4307697 Delivery Boy" mug.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Leela, have you seen the keys to the 
spaceship?

<character>LEELA</character>
I must've left them onboard.

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Eh, wha'? I mean, what?

<character>LEELA</character>
Relax. The ship's not going anywhere. 
I anchored it with the unbreakable diamond 
tether.

<info>The ship begins to rumble and slowly rises into the air. Leela 
and Farnsworth gasp.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. The coil of diamond tether starts 
to run out as the ship gets higher.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Meeting Room.</info>

<character>AMY</character>
Oh, no!

<info>She talks in Martian.</info>

<character>HERMES</character>
Sweet ghost of Babylon.

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
This isn't good for Zoidberg!

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. The ship emerges from the hangar 
and flies away. The tether tightens and the ship struggles, eventually 
ripping the building from it's foundations.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Woo, yeah!

<character>BENDER</character>
Woo-hoo!

<info>They laugh.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. The other five fly through the 
air and hit the back wall.</info>

<info>St. Louis. The ship flies under the Gateway Arch and loops the 
loop several times. The Planet Express building spins around 
it and the crew scream from inside.</info>

<info>San Francisco. The building skims the surface of the water by 
the Golden Gate Bridge.</info>

<info>Great Wall of China. The Chinese ignore the ship as it flies 
over. Seconds afterwards, the building crashes through the wall 
and the Mongols ride over it, wielding swords.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Fry sits with his feet on a console 
while Bender literally flies by the seat of his pants.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey, Fry, I'm steering with my ass!

<character>FRY</character>
That's the best thing I ever saw!

<info>Pisa. The ship knocks the Leaning Tower upright and the locals 
shout angrily at them and wave their fists.</info>

<character>ITALIAN #1</character>
You stink!

<info>The building hits it and knocks it at an angle again and the 
Italians cheer.</info>

<character>ITALIAN #1</character>
Alright, yeah!

<character>ITALIAN #2</character>
We like you a lot!

<info>The Leaning Tower topples and crushes some of them.</info>

<info>New New York City. The ship flies past the Statue of Liberty 
and over Manhattan before lowering the building back onto its 
foundations and landing in the hangar.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. The place is a tip. Fry and 
Bender walk down the ship's steps, laughing.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
That was great!

<character>BENDER</character>
And no one suspects a thing!  Whoa! 
And that's how we learned our lesson!

<info>Fry hides behind him and nods.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Farnsworth berates them.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
You've gone too far this time - all 
three of you!

<character>LEELA</character>
What did I do?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
You left the keys in the ignition. I 
mean, look at those two. Wasn't it obvious 
what would happen?

<character>FRY</character>
Yeah, Leela.

<character>BENDER</character>
We're all very disappointed in you.

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
I should fire you three right now, but 
I'm just not that cold-hearted.

<info>He whispers something to Hermes.</info>

<character>HERMES</character>
You're all fired.

<info>The others' jaws drop.</info>

<info>Outside Planet Express. The three former employees leave through 
the main door. Zoidberg, Amy, Hermes and Farnsworth watch them 
go.</info>

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Goodbye, friends. I'll miss you.  Good 
riddance to them. Now Zoidberg is the 
popular one!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Yes, yes! Let's all talk to Zoidberg.

<character>AMY</character>
Hey, Dr. Zoidberg, I've been thinking. 
Do you think we could go out?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
So, Zoidberg. What's new?

<character>HERMES</character>
Tell me, Zoidberg: Is it carapace or 
carapass?

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Oh, you know...!

<info>Park. The jobless Fry, Leela and Bender sit on a bench.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
What are we supposed to do for money? 
All I've got is my frequent taffy eater's 
card, my first moustache......and this 
picture of me and my old girlfriend, 
Michelle, and that ski instructor she 
was just friends with.

<info>In the photo the ski instructor has his arm around Michelle 
while Fry leans into the photo, waving. Bender unscrews his head 
and holds it out like a bucket to a passing man.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Pardon me, brother. Care to donate to 
the Anti-Mugging-You Fund?  Ow!

<info>She puts his head back on.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
We don't need to beg, Bender. For God's 
sake, we're not veterans!

<character>FRY</character>
Well, what do you suggest? A daring 
daylight robbery of Fort Knox on elephant-back? 
That's the dumbest thing I ever heard!

<character>LEELA</character>
No, we can get jobs.

<character>BENDER</character>
But we just had jobs!

<info>Leela opens her backpack.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Fortunately, I still have our old career 
chips.

<character>FRY</character>
Our what?

<character>LEELA</character>
Career chips.  You remember? They assign 
you the job you're best at.  I tried 
to give you one and you ran away.  It's 
how we met!

<character>FRY</character>
And then what happened?

<info>She sighs.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Just give me your hand.

<info>She clips him with her implant gun.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Ow!

<character>LEELA</character>
Baby!  Ow!

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Ipgee's Office. Leela reapplies to the company 
with the motto "It Seems To Work OK" at exactly 3pm. Fry and 
Bender are with her.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
I'd like to reapply for my old job: 
Counselling defrostees and assigning 
them careers.

<character>IPGEE</character>
Oh, I was hoping you would come back! 
I even saved your poster of a chimp 
expressing your distaste for Mondays.

<info>He takes the poster out of his drawer. It has a picture of a 
monkey wearing a tie on it. Above, "I Hate Mondays" is written.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Monday Monkey lives for the weekend, 
sir.

<character>IPGEE</character>
Just put your hand under the scanner 
so I can verify your career chip.  Calcutta, 
we have a problem.

<info>"Career: Delivery Boy" is on the screen.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Delivery boy? I must have mixed up the 
chips. It's a simple mis -

<info>Ipgee scans Fry's chip.</info>

<character>IPGEE</character>
Oh, here's a cryogenic counsellor! Do 
you like Mondays?

<character>FRY</character>
They're <character>OK</character>.

<character>IPGEE</character>
Then we'll have to redecorate your office. 
How do you feel about it helping to 
be crazy to work here but not being 
necessary?

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey, let's see what it says about me.

<info>He takes a severed human arm out of his chest cabinet and Ipgee 
scans it. "Prime Minister Of Norway" appears on the screen.</info>

<character>IPGEE</character>
Welcome aboard, sir.

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Freezer Room. Terry scrapes some condensation 
from the front of an active freezer tube. Fry is wearing a blue 
uniform and he and Bender are both wearing white coats.</info>

<character>TERRY</character>
Remember, when the tube opens, say...(dramatically)..."Welcome 
to the world of tomorrow!"

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, I was frozen. I think I know what 
people wanna hear when they first wake 
up.  Bathroom's that way.

<info>The man pushes him out the way and runs.</info>

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Probulator Room. The man is lying naked 
on the table. Hovering above him are some sharp instruments.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
So, while you're on the Probulator, 
tell me, what brings you to the future?

<character>MAN</character>
Oh, well, I wanted to meet Shakespeare 
and I figured that time was cyclical.

<character>FRY</character>
Nope. Straight line.  Ah, the Probulator's 
done.

<character>MAN</character>
That wasn't so bad.

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, wait, it hasn't started yet.  OK, 
it's about to start.

<info>It dings and the man screams some more.</info>

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Freezer Room. A freezer opens and an old 
man walk out, rubbing his eyes. Bender runs towards him wearing 
a giant fly's head and a cape.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Welcome to the future, human slave. 
Ah, relax, chum. I'm not really a giant 
fly!  I'm a horrible robot!  Kill all 
humans!

<info>The old man clutches his chest.</info>

<character>TERRY</character>
Dear God! He's having a heart attack!

<info>Bender pushes the old man into the freezer, turns the dial and 
freezer him.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Ah, they'll probably find a cure for 
that in the future.

<character>TERRY</character>
We have a cure for it now!

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh, good. Then you won't mind if I use 
this.

<info>He puts a gorilla mask on.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry is frozen in a freezer. It pings, unfreezes 
him and opens the door. He yawns and stretches.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Nothing like a power nap.

<info>He pours himself a coffee and opens the old man's tube. There 
are pizza boxes, milk cartons, beers and cans of Slurm stacked 
around him. Fry pours some milk in his coffee. The old man unfreezes.</info>

<character>OLD MAN</character>
Oh, flies! Flies and gorillas!

<info>Fry hands him the milk and closes the door. The old man freezes 
again. The door to the Probulator room opens and Bender walks 
out.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Stay beautiful, doll-face!  That Probulator 
sure knows how to please a man. So, 
what's for lunch?

<character>FRY</character>
I ordered a pizza.

<info>The door opens and Leela walks in, wearing delivery girl garb. 
Her cap has a slice of pizza stuck in it.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Pizza delivery for...I.C. Wiener.  Yeah, 
very funny. Now cough up the $12.95.

<character>FRY</character>
Sorry, but if it's not here in half 
an hour, it's free.

<character>LEELA</character>
It's only been 23 minutes.

<character>FRY</character>
Well, uh, I've got 33 minutes.

<info>Leela puts the pizza box on the table and presses a button. 
The doodle of a hef starts to talk.</info>

<character>CHEF</character>
It's only been-a 23 minutes, you dumb-a 
canolli. You got a problem, we can take 
it outside.

<character>FRY</character>
OK, I'll fight the box. I think I can 
take him.

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry, just pay me. I still owe 30 bucks 
on this uniform.

<character>CHEF</character>
35, you stupid meatball.

<info>Time Lapse. Bender and Fry walk past the freezers, looking at 
a clipboard.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Who should be unfreeze next?

<info>They look at a commando-type who is holding a gun and pulling 
a pin from a grenade.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
No.  No!  Oh, my God! It's Pauly Shore!

<character>BENDER</character>
Alright!

<info>He puts his gorilla mask on.</info>

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Probulator Room. Pauly Shore is lying on 
the table.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Mr. Shore, I loved you in Bio-Dome. 
You sure caused some trouble in that 
bubble!

<character>SHORE</character>
Rest assured, if it rhymes, I can cause 
trouble in it.

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, now that you're in the future, 
you can go live in an actual bio-dome!

<character>SHORE</character>
An unattractive prospect. While researching 
for the role, I ran computer simulations 
demonstrating, incontravertably, that 
the whole bio-enclosure concept is fundamentally 
flawed. Be it expressed via dome, sphere, 
cube or even a stately tetrahedron, 
buuuddy!

<info>He smacks his lips. Fry stares blankly at him.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Oh.  How did you wind up getting frozen?

<character>SHORE</character>
Well, while filming Encino Man my intellectual 
curiosity re: cryogenics was peaked, 
and I resolved to freeze the weasel.

<character>FRY</character>
The weasel?

<info>He laughs.</info>

<character>SHORE</character>
Hey, listen, skippy. I was supposed 
to be unfrozen in Hollywood for the 
thousandth anniversary screening of 
Jury Duty <character>II</character>. How come I'm not there?

<character>FRY</character>
I woke you up early so we could hang 
out and do stuff.

<character>SHORE</character>
Like what?

<info>Fry turns the Probulator on and Shore screams.</info>

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Freezer Room.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I love this job.

<info>Bender is wearing a sheet over his head and looks like a cartoon 
ghost.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Me too.

<info>A freezer pings.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Showtime! (hoarse) I'll pretend to be 
dying of space plague.

<info>The freezer opens and Fry gasps.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Boo?

<info>The condensation clears and the woman inside the freezer wakes 
up.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Michelle!

<info>Bender looks at the photo inside Fry's wallet.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh, my God!

<info>He steals some cash and hands the wallet back to Fry.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Fry? Is it really you?

<character>FRY</character>
I don't know. Is it really you?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
What do you mean you don't know? Are 
you you or not?

<character>FRY</character>
Who wants to know?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Oh, Fry, it is you!

<info>She hugs him and they kiss. Bender makes scary ghostie noises.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry and Michelle are sat down.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I don't get it, Michelle. The last time 
I saw you, you were doing great. You 
had just dumped me and you were well 
on your way to getting you life back 
on track. Why'd you freeze yourself?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Oh, Fry. After you left, things took 
a turn for the worse. I got married.

<character>FRY</character>
I'm sorry.

<info>Flashback. At Michelle's wedding, her new husband slips a ring 
onto her finger and they kiss.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
(voice-over) His name was Charles. He 
attended a law school so prestigious, 
the basketball team was coached by Ruth 
Bader Ginsberg.  I put him through law 
school by working as a dog walker for 
antisocial dogs.

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Sorry.

<info>Flashback. The scene moves to Charles's graduation.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
(voice-over) But soon after Charles 
graduated, our marriage ran into difficulties.

<info>Charles throws his hat into the air and Michelle catches it 
and sees him kissing another woman.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Uh, sorry.

<info>Flashback. Michelle walks the streets alone at night.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
(voice-over) Desperately depressed, 
I turned to the one thing that could 
lessen my pain: A carnival. Unfortunately, 
a corn dog bone got lodged in the control 
panel of the Spizzler, and I had to 
ride it for eight hours.

<character>FRY</character>
(voice-over) Sorry.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
(voice-over) But it did give me a chance 
to think...

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I'm sorry.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
...and I remembered the last time I 
was truly happy; When I was with you.

<character>FRY</character>
Aww. So you froze yourself to come look 
for me?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
No, I did it to get a fresh start. I 
didn't know what had happened to you 
- no one did. The police were going 
to conduct a search but your parents 
felt it was a waste of taxpayer money.

<character>FRY</character>
That's the same reason they kept me 
out of school. So, no one even cared 
that I was gone?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Not really. Except for one person.

<info>She puts her hand on his and they move closer.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Who was it?

<info>New New York City Streets. Fry and Michelle fly a hover-scooter 
over the city.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Everything is so different.

<character>FRY</character>
Not everything. There's still a roach 
problem.

<info>A giant roach flies beside them and Fry sprays it.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Ew!

<info>Museum Of Really Modern Art. The artwork is on the stomachs 
of lots of fat men. Michelle and Fry look at a painting on Sal.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Eurgh.

<character>FRY</character>
Nowadays, people aren't interested in 
art that's not tattooed on fat guys.

<character>SAL</character>
I'm on loan from the Louvre.

<info>Park. Fry and Michelle sit in a horse-drawn carriage. The cab 
man whips the horse and a giant bug whips him. He screams and 
Michelle whimpers.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Outside the building, repair work 
is being done. Inside, Leela and Bender meet with Farnsworth.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Please, professor. Give us our jobs 
back. We deserve another chance.

<character>BENDER</character>
Yeah, and if you won't give me another 
chance, perhaps you'd give one to......Og, 
gorilla emperor of Earth!

<info>The ship lands in the hangar.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
I'm sorry, Og, but I've got a new crew.

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. Farnsworth leans over the railings 
and Hermes, Amy and Zoidberg get off the ship.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
So, how was delivery to Fantasy Planet, 
where everyone's fantasies come to life?

<character>AMY</character>
Great!

<character>HERMES</character>
Organised!

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
For one beautiful night, I knew what 
it was to be a grandmother. Subjugated, 
yet honoured.

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Meeting Room. Bender has the gorilla 
mask under his arm and Farnsworth talks to it.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
You see, Og? Everything's running smoothly, 
yes. And with Fry fired, I can finally 
leave my jigsaw puzzles out without 
him eating the pieces.

<character>LEELA</character>
Forget about Fry. You can hire us back 
and he'd never have to know.

<info>Enter Fry.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Hey, guys.

<character>LEELA</character>
Oh. Hey, Fry!

<character>BENDER</character>
So, as Leela was saying, Fry can go 
shove a big old - Ow!

<info>Leela clocks him with a phone.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I'm glad you're all here. I wanted to 
introduce you to my on-again-off-again 
girlfriend of the past thousand years, 
Michelle.  Michelle, this is Leela. 
This is Bender.  The professor.  Hermes 
and Amy.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Nice to meet you.

<character>FRY</character>
And this is Dr. Zoidberg.

<info>Zoidberg screams and runs away.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Fry sits on the couch and Hermes, Bender 
and Farnsworth stand around him.</info>

<character>HERMES</character>
Dating you ex, Fry? Have you lost all 
self-respect?

<character>FRY</character>
All what?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
This can only end badly, Fry. Kids, 
a house -

<character>BENDER</character>
A home invasion by a former roommate.

<character>FRY</character>
But things are different this time. 
Before, she was demanding and possessive. 
But now she wants me to do stuff and 
stay with her all the time.

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Amy and Michelle sit at the table. 
Zoidberg, wearing a frilly apron, pours them some tea.</info>

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
There you go, dearies.

<info>He hums and leaves. Michelle trembles.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
It's a relief to meet you, Amy. I'm 
just having a hard time adjusting to 
all the strange stuff here in the future.

<character>AMY</character>
I'm from Mars.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
I feel so out of place here. I don't 
understand why Fry fits in so well.

<character>LEELA</character>
Probably because he didn't fit in back 
in your time.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
That's true. But I used to fit in really 
well.

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Then good luck, sister.

<info>He screams and walks off. Michelle drops her cup and it smashes. 
Seconds later it reassembles itself. She whimpers.</info>

<info>Applied Cryogenics: Freezer Room.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Don't take this the wrong way, Fry, 
but your friends are a bunch of freaks.

<character>FRY</character>
Yeah, they're great, huh?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
I just don't belong here. I don't know 
anyone, I can't find a vanishing cream 
that doesn't make me actually vanish. 
I don't even have a job.

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, right. I was supposed to assign 
you a job. Let me just get your career 
chip installed.  Hold out your palm. 
What are you scared of? It's just like 
getting your hand pierced.

<info>Michelle pushes the gun away.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
This world is horrible. Let's start 
over, Fry. Well go someplace where all 
we have is each other.

<character>FRY</character>
Ooh, romantic. I'll tell Bender to meet 
us there.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
It's not a "there". It's a "then".  
The future.

<character>FRY</character>
Whoa, whoa, girl. I thought you were 
talking about one of those motels where 
the bed is shaped like stuff.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
I love you. Don't you love me?

<character>FRY</character>
Well, sure. To the extent a man can 
love a woman. But this seems like a 
big step.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Fry, why must you analyse everything 
with your relentless logic? Nothing 
matters but our love.

<character>FRY</character>
You're right. Let's do this now and 
let's never regret it.

<info>They climb into the freezer and kiss. They are frozen in a flash.</info>

<info>Apocalyptic Wasteland. The freezer stands alone in a vast desert. 
The door opens and Fry and Michelle get out and look around. 
The ruins of buildings burn and there are cracks in the ground.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Michelle, I don't regret this. But I 
both rue and lament it.

<info>Time Lapse. The pair walk the desert.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
The year 4000 is severely disappointing. 
I miss the year 3000 when life was simple 
and brains flew through space and everyone 
ate lasers.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
It's not that bad. Fate brought us together 
and now fate brought us here.

<character>FRY</character>
No, you brought us here.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Whine some more, Fry, I really find 
that attractive in a man. Now come on, 
build us a shelter.

<character>FRY</character>
Alright, fine. Everything else sucks. 
At least we can have a nice place to 
live.

<info>Time Lapse. It is dark and Fry is covered in dirt.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Ooh, there.

<info>He is standing in a hole.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
You expect me to live in a tiny little 
hole?

<character>FRY</character>
It'd be deeper, but I'm standing on 
a gopher.

<info>Time Lapse. The next morning, Fry and Michelle are woken up 
by someone poking their faces with sticks.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Oh, look. Some little kids.

<character>FRY</character>
They'll save us.  We're saved!

<info>Kids' Den. Fry and Michelle are tied up in the middle of the 
den, which is in the middle of some ruined buildings. One of 
the kids sits on a chair, elevated by some oil drums.</info>

<character>BUTCH</character>
I'm Butch, leader of this place. I took 
your hole and you can't do nothing about 
it.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
<character>OK</character>.

<character>FRY</character>
Mighty sir, we have nowhere to go. Could 
we please join your society?

<character>BUTCH</character>
Well, alright. But no interfering with 
our grand works.

<info>Time Lapse. The kids smash an old couch to bits and fight. Butch 
watches them and nods. Fry joins Michelle, who is lying on a 
sun bed.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I tell you, that Butch runs a pretty 
good civilisation. I think I'll enjoy 
serving under him.

<info>Michelle groans.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
You know your problem, Fry? You're not 
ambitious. You should be chief.

<character>FRY</character>
What do I need, ulcers?

<character>MICHELLE</character>
But I want power. I'm tired of the chief's 
girlfriend lording it over me with her 
fancy coyote hide.

<info>They watch Butch's girlfriend stroking the hide.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Alright, alright. If it'll make you 
happy, I'll overthrow society.

<info>Time Lapse. Butch laughs.</info>

<character>BUTCH</character>
On what grounds do you challenge my 
authority?

<character>FRY</character>
Well, I'm older than you. I can beat 
you up.

<info>The kids nod.</info>

<character>KID #1</character>
Yeah, I'll bet he could.

<character>BUTCH</character>'S <character>GIRLFRIEND</character>
He's got arm hair.

<character>BUTCH</character>
Alright, grandpa. There's only one way 
to settle this. Death rolling!

<info>The kids cheer.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
What's death rolling?

<character>OROWHEAT</character>
It's like skateboarding.

<character>ICE</character>-V
Except half the time, someone dies.

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, so it's a little safer than skateboarding.

<info>Ruined City. At the top of a ruined building, Fry stands on 
a skateboard with wheels and Butch stands on a rocket-propelled 
one.</info>

<character>BUTCH</character>
Last one holding the bandana's the new 
leader.

<info>He takes his bandana off and Fry holds one end of it.</info>

<character>MICHELLE</character>
My mother always said you were a loser, 
Fry. Now get out there and prove her 
wrong.

<character>FRY</character>
(sadly) Beth said that?

<character>BUTCH</character>'S <character>GIRLFRIEND</character>
(in Hebrew) One, two, three.

<info>Butch flies down the ramp, dragging Fry with him. They tug back 
and forth on the bandana as they wind through the ruined streets. 
Butch pulls Fry through a sewer pipe and Fry's hair makes sparks 
on the side of it. They leave the sewer pipe and jump on a highway. 
Two urban defence vehicles drive either side of them and start 
shooting at each other. They flip over and Fry and Butch dodge 
them. Fry rolls down the opposite lane, straight towards an oncoming 
car. He lifts his skateboard onto the other side, missing the 
car. Butch holds onto the bumper of a car and Fry grabs the bumper 
of another one. He coughs as he gets exhaust in his face. The 
cars split and Fry and Butch fly towards a lamppost. The bandana 
wraps around it and their heads hit each other. The kids and 
Michelle gather around.</info>

<character>BUTCH</character>
It's cool. Back off.  (crying) My knee. 
I scraped it.

<character>FRY</character>
Aww. Poor little guy. Let me just take 
a look at - aha!  I won! I'm the new 
chief! I'm the tallest and I weigh the 
most!

<info>The kids takes their guns out.</info>

<character>BUTCH</character>
Hand it over, you giant idiot.

<info>An armoured car pulls up and honks its horn.</info>

<character>BUTCH</character>'S <character>GIRLFRIEND</character>
Hey, Butch, your mom's here.

<character>BUTCH</character>
Aw, man.

<character>BUTCH</character>'S <character>MOM</character>
Come on, kids. You're late for Hebrew 
school.

<info>The kids groan and drop their guns.</info>

<character>OROWHEAT</character>
I don't wanna go.

<character>BUTCH</character>'S <character>GIRLFRIEND</character>
Every Monday and Wednesday's the same 
thing.

<info>They get into the car and drive away.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
I find this post-apocalyptic wasteland 
very confusing. Seriously, I'm weirded 
out.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
That's because you're a loser. You were 
a loser in the year 2000 and you're 
a loser in the year 4000.

<character>FRY</character>
Yeah, but in the year 3000, I had it 
all. Several friends, a low-paying job, 
a bed in a robot's closet. I envied 
no man. But you wrecked everything.

<character>MICHELLE</character>
Quit standing up for yourself, Fry. 
When we get back to the hole, we are 
going to have a long, boring talk about 
our relationship!

<character>FRY</character>
Oh, yeah? Well, listen to this: (whispering) 
I'm leaving you.

<info>He runs away.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry walks alone through the misty desert.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
There must be people somewhere.

<info>He climbs a small hill and sees some lights in the distance. 
He slips on some loose stones and bounces down the other side 
of the hill.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The mist is thicker. Fry falls to the ground. The 
mist clears a little and something comes into view.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Yes! Footprints! And hand prints?  But? 
What's happening?

<info>He stands up and sees Loew's Gaddafi's Chinese Theater in front 
of him. He steps back. The Planet Express ship lands beside him, 
crushing a floodlight. People scatter. Leela, Bender and Farnsworth 
walk off the ship.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry, thank God we found you.

<character>FRY</character>
Leela? What are you guys doing here 
in the year 4000?

<character>LEELA</character>
It's not the year 4000.

<character>BENDER</character>
You were only frozen for two days. Uh, 
by the way, I broke your bed.

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
You were in Pauly Shore's tube and they 
were delivering it to his movie screening.

<info>He points to the sign on the theatre; "Jury Duty II: Trouble 
On The Hubble Starring Dr. Paul Shore. 1000th Anniversary Gala!"</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
But, when they noticed you weren't him, 
they chucked you in a ditch.

<character>FRY</character>
So you're saying these aren't the decaying 
ruins of New York in the year 4000?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
You wish! You're in Los Angeles!

<character>FRY</character>
But there was this gang of 10-year olds 
with guns.

<character>LEELA</character>
Exactly: You're in L.A.

<character>FRY</character>
But everyone is driving around in cars 
shooting at each other.

<character>BENDER</character>
That's L.A.. for you.

<character>FRY</character>
But the air's green and there's no sign 
of civilisation whatsoever.

<character>BENDER</character>
He just won't stop with the social commentary.

<character>FRY</character>
And the people are all phoneys. No one 
reads. Everything has cilantro on it 
-  Michelle, baby!

<character>MICHELLE</character>
It's not working out, Fry.

<info>The limo drives away. Pauly Shore pokes his head out of the 
sunroof.</info>

<character>SHORE</character>
(shouting) Tis better to have loved 
and lost, n'est ce-pas?

<info>He laughs.</info>

<info>Ship's Cockpit. Fry looks out of the window as the ship flies 
back to New New York.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
That's it. I've had it with women. From 
now on, I'm concentrating on my career. 
Can I have my old job back?

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Why, I've forgotten why I even fired 
you.

<character>BENDER</character>
'Cause he destroyed your business, your 
home and all your possessions.

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Oh, that's right. Get lost.

<info>He pulls a lever and the floor opens up beneath Fry. He falls 
out of the ship and screams.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>