<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 404

<title>LOVE AND ROCKET</title>

<author>Dan Vebber</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: When You See The Robot, Drink!</info>

<info>Ship's Cockpit. Bender argues with the ship at a port that looks 
like the ports <character>HAL 9000</character> used in 2001: A Space Oddysey. The ship 
speaks with a male voice.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
You are one narrow minded spaceship 
Planet Express Ship.

<character>SHIP</character>
Whoa whoa! Why should my tax money pay 
for art I find offensive?

<info>Bender flips through a book titled Art &amp; You and holds up a 
page with a picture of a Horrible Gelatinous Blob.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Would you censor the Venus de Venus 
just because you can see her spewers?

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh its filthy! Why not create a national 
endowment for strip clubs while we're 
at it?

<character>BENDER</character>
Why not indeed!

<character>LEELA</character>
Bender! Ship! Stop bickering or I'm 
going to come back there and change 
your opinions manually!

<character>BENDER</character>
Fine! I'll be in my quarters appreciating 
controversial artworks.

<info>He leaves. The door closes on him and cuts his head off. It 
lands on the floor and rolls a little.</info>

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>SARCASTICALLY</character>)
Oops! Sorry!

<info>He chuckles.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The crew are sat around the table. 
Bender screws his head back on.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Ah that ship is so white bread!

<info>Enter Hermes and Farnsworth carrying several red boxes.</info>

<character>HERMES</character>
People! It's Valentines Day next week, 
so your beloved company has gotten you 
all new uniforms!

<info>Everyone opens their boxes and reacts well to the uniforms.</info>

<character>AMY</character>
Cool!

<character>ZOIDBERG</character>
Clothing, delicious clothing!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
We'll need to look our best if we're 
to get the account of our new potential 
customer Romanticorp!

<character>AMY</character>
Romanticorp? Are they a corporation 
that makes romantic stuff?

<character>HERMES</character>
Very good Amy!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Everyone suit up. We're off to the most 
romantic city on Earth!

<info>Milwaukee. The ship flies in and lands in the Romanticorp factory. 
The doors have lips painted on them and make kissy sounds when 
they close.</info>

<info>Cut to: Romanticorp Factory Entrance.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Remember, we've got to show these people 
we're not bitter husks of human beings 
who long ago abandoned hope of finding 
love in this lifetime. Leela you'll 
have to do some acting.

<character>LEELA</character>
Check!

<info>Some doors open and a man and a woman, Sheldon and Gwen, walk 
in.</info>

<character>SHELDON</character>
Welcome, aww I'm just so excited!  I'm 
Sheldon and this is my chief financial 
officer Gwen.

<character>GWEN</character>
For 30 years we've shared the adventure 
of managing Romanticorp.

<character>SHELDON</character>
Not to mention the adventure of marriage!

<info>They both laugh. Then they kiss again.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Oh you have got to be kidding!  Ow! 
Ow! I mean, aww thats so sweet!  Ow! 
I mean, (soppily) Aww dats show shweet!

<info>Farnsworth nods.</info>

<info>Romanticorp Factory Production Line. The crew and Sheldon and 
Gwen are moving along a moving walkway.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
You know, romance is an important part 
of our work too, uh right everyone?

<info>The crew nod in agreement.</info>

<character>SHELDON</character>
Do any of you collect Lovey Bears?

<character>AMY</character>
I do! Kif's given me dozens! Is it true 
what the ad says? That you kiss them 
together out of blanket cloth and magic 
buttons?

<character>GWEN</character>
No.

<character>SHELDON</character>
It's actually cheaper to genetically 
engineer real ones.  They frolic in 
the Lovey Forest until their first birthday 
then we choose the cuddliest ugliest 
ones and stuff them full of fire retardant 
love fluff!

<info>In the Lovey Forest, bears are picked up and put onto a conveyor 
belt where they are delivered to the Bear "Hospital".</info>

<character>AMY </character>(<character>UNSURE</character>)
Oh cute!

<info>Romanticorp Factory Romance Acceleration Lab.</info>

<character>GWEN</character>
Knowing which pickup lines fizzle and 
which ones sizzle keeps us on the cutting 
edge of flirtation technology.

<info>Two robot frames stand in front of a woman.</info>

<character>FRAME #1</character>
Is heaven missing an angel? 'Cause you've 
got nice cans!

<info>The woman is not impressed.</info>

<character>FRAME #2</character>
My two favourite things are commitment 
and changing myself.

<info>The woman is lovestruck and hugs the frame.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Does that dummy have a brother?

<info>Romanticorp Factory Candy Hearts Production.</info>

<character>SHELDON</character>
And now friends and lovers we come to 
the heart of our operation. Pun definately 
intended!

<info>He and Gwen laugh. Leela sighs. Farnsworth threatens her with 
the cattle prod. Hermes picks up a candy heart that says "Cutie 
Pie."</info>

<character>HERMES</character>
Impressive!

<character>GWEN</character>
My family has been making these hearts 
since the 1900's. Tastes may have changed 
but our secret recipe sure hasn't.

<info>She points to a machine mixing Bone Meal and Earwig Honey. Fry 
picks up a candy heart.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Whoa! Letters like "U" and "R" can mean 
words like "You" and "Are." Here Leela, 
U-R-2 Cute!

<character>LEELA</character>
Perhaps. What's your point?

<character>FRY</character>
I've never been able to put into words 
how I feel about you. But somewhere 
among these trillions of hearts, those 
words must already exist. And I'm gonna 
find them.

<info>He dives into a barrel and rummages around. A Lovey Bear runs 
around being chased by a hunter. The hunter shoots and misses. 
Farnsworth zaps the Lovey Bear with the cattle prod and it falls 
over. He turns to Sheldon and Gwen.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
So, do we have the contract?

<info>Ship's Cockpit. The ship is now back in the hangar and the crew 
have changed back into their normal clothes.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
With that big new Romanticorp contract, 
I've been able to make those government 
mandated upgrades you've all been suing 
me about.

<info>The crew look around the cockpit.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Ooo look! You taped up the cracks in 
the dark matter reactor!

<character>FRY</character>
And you got a cage for the lion!

<info>The cage is in the ceiling. The lion growls and swipes it's 
paw at Fry. Bender turns the radio on.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey who's been messing with the radio? 
This isn't alternative rock. It's college 
rock!

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
Oh it must have been the ship's new 
improved personality software I installed.

<character>SHIP</character>
Yeah it was me. It's a cute song.

<character>BENDER</character>
Listen ship! No one changes my stations! 
I hope you have a good mechanic!

<info>He rolls his sleeves up.</info>

<character>FARNSWORTH</character>
It even comes with an adjustable voice.

<info>He adjusts the voice. As the ship speaks its voice changes from 
the smartarse male voice to a friendly female voice.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
We each get one of the four buttons 
remember Bender? That was the deal.

<info>She giggles.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Wha? Did you just say...?

<character>SHIP</character>
If you don't like the stations you could 
just...play with my buttons 'til you 
find something we both enjoy.  Oh gosh! 
That came out all wrong!

<character>BENDER</character>
Too late baby, you said it! So what'll 
it be? My place? Or you?

<info>Time Lapse. The crew are now in uniform and are cruising through 
space. Fry enters with a barrel of candy hearts.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Before we deliver these hearts, I'm 
gonna find the one that sums up my feelings 
for you!  "I Love You." Hmm, too conventional. 
"You're My Man." Ooo so close!

<character>LEELA</character>
I'm not impressed by a guy's message 
Fry. I'm impressed by the guy. Or not.

<info>The ship shakes violently. Fry falls over.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Whoa!

<character>LEELA</character>
What was that?

<character>FRY</character>
Maybe we hit a space cow.

<info>Cut to: Ship's Engine Room. Bender is tickling a control panel.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Coochie coochie!

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>GIGGLING</character>)
Stop it! You're mussing up my trajectory!

<character>BENDER</character>
You know you love it sugar-engine!

<info>He presses some buttons.</info>

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>GIGGLING</character>)
No!

<info>She laughs. Enter Fry and Leela.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Bender!  What's going on in here?  Planet 
Express Ship! Cover your shame!

<info>Ship closes the control panel.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
It's not what it looks like. Bender 
was just helping me...zip up my turbine.

<character>FRY</character>
Wow Bender. Are you and the ship an 
item? I mean I know you're both items 
but...how can you date a ship anyway? 
It'd be like me dating a really fat 
lady. And living inside her. And she'd 
be all like...

<info>He impersonates a ship.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Fry, in order for me to get busy at 
maximum efficiency, I need a girl with 
a big 400 ton booty!

<info>He taps the wall.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Bender, dating your co-worker and primary 
mode of transportation is immoral, illogical 
and a violation of interstellar shipping 
statute 437-B.

<character>BENDER</character>
That's what makes it so nasty!

<info>He strokes the control panel. Ship giggles. He giggles and rubs 
himself up the wall.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Still, given the chance, I've given 
to urges far more shocking.

<info>Bender starts rubbing a girder.</info>

<info>Musical Scene. Bender sings A Bicycle Made For Two while he 
dates the ship. First he sits on one of the tail fins with a 
picnic set up. The sheet blows in the breeze of space.</info>

<character>BENDER </character>(<character>SINGING</character>)
Daisy, Daisy, give me your answer do. 
I'm half crazy all for the love of 
you.  It won't be a stylish marriage......I 
can't afford a carriage.  But you'll 
look sweet upon the seat of a bicycle 
built for two.

<info>On the hangar roof Bender and Ship dance under the moonlight.

[Planet Express: Meeting Room. Leela reads a newspaper while 
Fry is still searching for the perfect candy heart.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Well, I'm sick of her.

<character>FRY</character>
The ship? But you just started dating.

<character>BENDER</character>
With my mighty robot powers I can get 
sick of things much quicker than you 
humans.

<character>LEELA</character>
Well just remember we all still have 
to work together. So try and let her 
down easy.

<character>BENDER</character>
In due time Leela. But for now I'll 
just resume dating cheap floozies on 
the side.

<character>FRY</character>
You have much to teach us.

<character>LEELA</character>
Ugh. Doesn't it bother you even a little 
to be taking advantage of your girlfriend's 
trust?

<info>Bender laughs.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Oh wait you're serious. Let me laugh 
even harder.

<info>He laughs even harder.</info>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine. Bender sits with two Fembots. They giggle.</info>

<character>FEMBOT #1</character>
What's it like being a lawyer for the 
Mayor's office? And also the world's 
strongest millionaire?

<character>BENDER</character>
Well baby, for starters you gotta be 
honest all the time!

<info>Enter Elzar.</info>

<character>ELZAR</character>
Good evening Bender! And to your lady 
friends may I say - Bam!

<info>The Fembots giggle.</info>

<character>FEMBOT #2</character>
You know Elzar?

<info>Through a window Ship watches Bender and the Fembots.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Elzar's Fine Cuisine. Ship sighs.</info>

<info>Robot Arms Apartments: Fry and Bender's Apartment. In Fry's 
room the windowbell ding dongs and awakens Fry. He opens the 
window. It is Ship.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Planet Express Ship? Is that you?

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh. Hi Fry. Is Bender home?

<character>FRY</character>
Uh, um no. I think he's at his parent's.

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh I see. He didn't fly there in another 
spaceship did he?

<character>FRY</character>
Bender? No! He's an old fashioned one 
spaceship robot. Look I'll tell him 
you stopped by OK?

<character>SHIP</character>
<character>OK</character>.

<info>Fry closes the window and walks back to his bed. Almost immediately 
the windowbell goes off again. He walks over and opens the window. 
Ship is still there.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh. Hi Fry. Is he home now?

<info>Central Park Zoo. Bender and the ship stroll around.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
Of all the zoos we've been to today, 
I like this one the best. Bender, which 
is your favourite nocturnal rat?

<character>BENDER</character>
Eh, they're all pretty unimpressive.

<info>The ship swoops off in another direction.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh honey look! The Tapirs!  It says 
here that the babies lose their pyjama 
like coat after their first year. Isn't 
that interesting honey?

<character>BENDER</character>
Yup. Mind numbingly interesting. Ooh!

<info>He spies a Fembot and zooms in on her.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
Bender!! Are you looking at other women?

<character>BENDER</character>
No baby never!

<info>He turns around. His eyes are fully zoomed.</info>

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>CRYING</character>)
Bender! Don't lie! I saw you at Elzar's 
with those two ladys of the evening. 
Explain that!

<character>BENDER</character>
OK, I like a challenge.  Aah! I got 
it! I'm going to be completely honest 
with you Planet Express ship. Those 
women you saw me with...were my accountants!

<character>SHIP</character>
Your accountants? Oh I would dearly 
love to believe that were true. So I 
do.

<character>BENDER</character>
Phew!

<character>SHIP</character>
I'm going to go home and get dinner 
started.

<info>She zooms off. Bender's chest cabinet opens. Lucy Liu's head 
in a jar is still there.</info>

<character>LIU</character>
Who are you talking to?

<character>BENDER</character>
No one baby! Lucy Liu is the only girl 
for Bender!

<character>LIU</character>
I love you -

<info>He slams the door on her.</info>

<info>Ship's Cockpit. Leela is steering the ship through an asteroid 
belt and is back in her new uniform. Ship sighs.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Planet Express Ship is something wrong?

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh it's Bender. He's acting so strange 
lately.  Do you think he's going to 
ask me to marry him?

<character>LEELA</character>
Uh, no.

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh-oh, someone knows something she's 
not telling!

<info>Leela sighs.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Uh look, I'm not saying Bender's not 
great but have you ever considered that 
maybe he's...y'know...not that great?

<info>Ship scoffs.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
You're just jealous! No one loves you 
because you're tiny and made of meat!

<info>An asteroid suddenly hits Ship's windscreen.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Could you maybe pay a little more attention 
to these asteroids?

<character>SHIP</character>
Sorry Captain Leela. I guess I'm just 
having one of those...manic Mondays!

<info>She laughs insanely. Leela laughs unsurely and then grins unsurely.</info>

<info>Ship flies towards Omicron Persei 8 (246/7 Days Without Invading 
Earth) and lands outside a huge castle, home of the planets' 
rulers, Lrrr and Nd-Nd.

[Cut to: Omicronian Castle. Lrrr and Nd-Nd watch <character>TV</character>.</info>

<character>LRRR</character>
This is ancient Earth's most foolish 
program. Why does Ross, the largest 
Friend, not simply eat the other five?

ND-ND
Perhaps they are saving that for sweeps.

<info>Enter a guard.</info>

<character>GUARD</character>
Exaulted leaders, the Earth messengers 
have arrived bearing a peace offering 
from their weak and fearful government.

<character>LRRR</character>
Oh very well. This is a Joey heavy episode 
anyway.

<info>He turns the TV off. Enter Leela, Fry and Bender with the barrels 
of candy hearts.</info>

<character>LRRR</character>
I am Lrrr of the planet Omicron Persei 
8.

<info>A picture slips from the wall. He puts it back. Leela reads 
from a piece of paper.</info>

<character>LEELA </character>(<character>READING</character>)
Esteemed potentates of Omicron Persei 
8, please accept these 20 billion candy 
hearts as proof that Earth loves you. 
Thiiis much!

<info>She holds her arms out wide. Lrrr and Nd-Nd taste the candy 
hearts. They immediately spit them out.</info>

<character>LRRR</character>
Bleurgh! These candies are choccy and 
unpleasant!

ND-ND
And what is this emotion you humans 
call "wuv"?

<character>LRRR</character>
Surely it says "love"?

ND-ND
No, "wuv." With an Earth "w." Behold!

<character>LRRR </character>(<character>SHOUTING</character>)
This concept of wuv confuses and infuriates 
us!

<info>Guards surround the crew, guns at the ready.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. The ship and crew have taken off and 
are pursued by Omicronian saucers.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Incoming torpedoes. Shields at maximum 
yarnell.

<character>LEELA</character>
Steady, Planet Express Ship. Focus on 
diverting all power to the scramjets.

<character>BENDER</character>
Uh look, Planet Express Ship, this might 
not be the best time...but...well...I 
really like you and whatever but...I 
think we should just be friends.

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>SCREAMING</character>)
Nooo!

<info>Cut to: Outside Ship. She jerks to a stop.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
So we're cool?

<info>The Omicronian torpedoes hit the ship and explode.</info>

<info>Time Lapse: The ship is tumbling through space with black scars 
on the hull. Ship is crying. Leela prints a readout from a machine 
and looks at it.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Well, it was a spectacular battle but 
there doesn't seem to be any permanent 
damage.

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>CRYING</character>)
No damage? What about my feelings?

<character>LEELA</character>
Aww, calm down. I'm sure Bender is taking 
this just as hard as you are.

<info>Cut to: Fry and Bender's Quarters. They are both lying in their 
hammocks.</info>

<character>BENDER </character>(<character>SINGING</character>)
Bender is great oh Bender is great. 
Bender Bender Bender!

<character>FRY</character>
You couldn't have picked a better time 
to dump the ship Bender!

<character>BENDER</character>
Eh, the moment seemed right. Call me 
old fashioned but I like a dump to be 
as memorable as it is devastating.

<info>Ship's Cockpit. It is nighttime ship's time. Ship is still crying. 
Leela is wearing her pyjamas and is sat in her chair facing Ship's 
port. She starts eating another tub of ice cream.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
I know, I know. Look Ship, if there's 
one thing I learnt from my mutual breakup 
with Sean that was totally mutual its 
that happiness can only come from within 
you.

<character>SHIP </character>(<character>CRYING</character>)
But Bender is within me! There must 
be some way to make him love me again.

<character>LEELA</character>
Trust me. You can't change men anymore 
than you can change the laws of time 
and space.

<character>SHIP</character>
That's so true.  I may not be able to 
change the laws of time and space, but 
I know something that can.

<info>Leela turns around and looks through the windscreen. She gasps. 
The ship is heading straight towards a huge quasar. She wrestles 
with the controls but they won't move.</info>

<character>LEELA </character>(<character>UNSURE</character>)
Uh sweetie? You see that giant quasar 
we're heading into? You might wanna 
scooch a few parsecs to the left.

<info>Ship, the movie buff, resonds calmly.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
I'm afraid I can't do that Leela.

<info>Enter Fry and Bender.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
What's happening? Space cow?

<character>LEELA</character>
The ship's just taking the breakup a 
little hard. (whispering to Fry) She's 
nuts!

<character>SHIP</character>
In a few moments the power of 10 million 
black holes will smush me and Bender 
together into a beautiful enternal quantum 
singularity.

<info>The crew scream.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Uh you don't need to kill us Planet 
Express ship...because...I love you! 
Uh yeah baby! I feel like doing stuff.

<character>SHIP</character>
Hmm. I don't believe you. If you really 
wanted to be with me you'd merge your 
program with mine.

<character>BENDER</character>
Whoa whoa whoa! Slow down! All of my 
friends that have done that said that 
afterwards all the passion went out 
of their relationship.

<character>LEELA</character>
Look, I don't know if you want my opinion 
-

<character>SHIP</character>
Leela. Bender and I really need to be 
alone. So, I'm turning off the oxygen.

<info>The oxygen goes off and Leela and Fry start to suffocate. They 
grab some oxygen tanks and put them on.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Now look missy! If you don't trun around 
now I'm going to have to shut down your 
brain!

<character>SHIP</character>
Fire detected in the vicinity of Leela.

<info>A fire hose comes down from the ceiling and hits Leela with 
a jet of water.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Ha! That barely hurt Leela at all!

<character>SHIP</character>
Maybe not. But what if the artificial 
gravity were to malfunction?

<info>The gravity goes off and Fry, Leela and Bender float towards 
the ceiling. The candy hearts float upwards and out of the barrels. 
Bender screams.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Float for your lives!

<info>They all swim through the door.</info>

<info>Ship's Bathroom. The crew get into the shower and Leela closes 
the door.</info>

<info>Cut to: Shower.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
This is the one place she can't hear 
us. Everyone just pretend to shower.

<character>FRY</character>
Same as everyday, got it.

<character>LEELA</character>
Now here's the plan.

<info>Cut to: Ship's Bathroom. Ship has another port in the bathroom. 
She tries to listen to the plan but can't hear through the soundproof 
shower glass. All she sees is Leela's lips moving.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
Oh, if only I could read lips!

<info>Cut to: Shower.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Comprendez Bender? You'll have to distract 
her. Merge your program with hers while 
I shut down her brain.

<character>BENDER</character>
It's too risky. I'm a very meek individual. 
If her personality engulfs mine, the 
Bender you know and worship could disappear 
forever!

<info>Leela doesn't take long to think about the situation.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
I'm willing to take that risk.

<info>Ship's Cockpit. The ship gets closer to the quasar. Bender floats 
in. There are candy hearts everywhere.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Hey pookums! Contrary to what I was 
saying earlier, melding minds with you 
would be extremely bearable.

<info>Ship gasps.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
You really mean it?

<character>BENDER</character>
Uh......yes!

<info>He pulls out a wire from inside the control panel and connects 
himself via a modem.</info>

<info>Ship's Mind. The Tron-esque environment looks sort of like a 
motherboard. Bender looks around in a panic. Ship is a little 
smaller and she has eyes and is wearing lipstick.</info>

<character>BENDER</character>
Huh? Tubes? You're older than you said 
you were!

<character>SHIP</character>
Come closer Bender. Lets become one!

<character>BENDER</character>
I prefer two. That way we can still 
be a horse for Hallowe'en.

<info>Ship moves closer to Bender. He backs away.</info>

<info>Ship's Brain Room. Fry and Leela float in. There are candy hearts 
floating around. Leela waves her hand across one of Ship's ports. 
No reaction.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
OK, Bender has her distracted. Now I 
can shut down her brain by deactivating 
the carbonated logic matrix.  Ugh. I 
can't concentrate with this obnoxious 
candy in my face.

<character>FRY</character>
I'm on it. And maybe I'll find those 
magic words while I'm at it.

<character>LEELA</character>
Fat chance.

<character>FRY</character>
Eh.  Blech!  Eurgh! Ooo how 'bout this 
one?

<character>LEELA</character>
Give it up Fry! I've got to pop these 
tops in a precise order.

<info>She pops another one. Fry sadly eats another heart.</info>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Halfway there. The ship should be getting 
a little less rational now.

<info>Cut to: Ship's Mind. Ship is chasing Bender making irrational 
noises.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
Want...to...engulf...Bender!

<info>She cackles and grows fangs.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Brain Room.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Only a few more.  Hey! I won free admission 
to Six Flags! Just one more reason we 
must survive this.

<info>Fry is about to eat another heart but notices Leela's oxygen 
gauge. The needle points at critical.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Um, Leela?

<character>LEELA</character>
Fry! I'll read your candy later! When 
we're not dead!  What was that?

<character>FRY </character>(<character>SUFFOCATING</character>)
Oh nothing.

<info>Cut to: Ship's Mind. Ship is still chasing Bender. He comes 
to a dead end on the motherboard.</info>

<character>SHIP</character>
We're gonna love being each other you 
sexy ion!

<character>BENDER </character>(<character>SCREAMING</character>)
Nooo!

<info>She moves towards him.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Brain Room.</info>

<character>LEELA</character>
Last one!  It worked! Gravity normal, 
air returning, terror replaced by cautious 
optimism! We did it Fry!  Fry?  You 
gave me your oxygen? Oh no! Breathe 
Fry breathe!  You leave me breathless! 
Happy Valentine's Day Fry!

<character>FRY </character>(<character>GASPING</character>)
Happy Valentine's day.

<info>Ship's Cockpit. Bender has separated from the ship. He wakes 
up. Enter Fry and Leela.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Bender! Are you OK?

<character>BENDER</character>
Aw. What crazy thing am I going to date 
next?

<character>LEELA</character>
Well at least it sounds like you were 
able to keep your conciousness seperate 
from hers.

<character>BENDER</character>
Of course! Bender is a lone wolf. A 
solitary eagle.  A cuddly baby Tapir! 
And that's why I love 'em!

<info>He walks out.</info>

<character>FRY</character>
Well I guess we'd better clean up these 
millions of hearts.

<character>LEELA</character>
Nah, I've got a lazier idea.

<info>The ship's cargo bay doors open and the candy hearts float out 
and into the quasar.</info>

<info>As he speaks shots of couples on Earth come and go. Horrible 
Gelatinous Blobs, mutants, Amy and Kif and Fry and Leela (joined 
by Zoidberg).</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>